<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Active-Active Redis applications on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/</link><description>Recent content in Active-Active Redis applications on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/databases/active-active/develop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Develop applications with Active-Active databases</title><link>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/develop-for-aa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/develop-for-aa/</guid><description>Developing geo-distributed, multi-master applications can be difficult. Application developers may have to understand a large number of race conditions between updates to various sites, network, and cluster failures that could reorder the events and change the outcome of the updates performed across geo-distributed writes.
Active-Active databases (formerly known as CRDB) are geo-distributed databases that span multiple Redis Enterprise Software (RS) clusters. Active-Active databases depend on multi-master replication (MMR) and Conflict-free Replicated Data Types (CRDTs) to power a simple development experience for geo-distributed applications.</description></item><item><title>Application failover with Active-Active databases</title><link>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/app-failover-active-active/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/app-failover-active-active/</guid><description>Active-Active Redis deployments don&amp;rsquo;t have a built-in failover or failback mechanism for application connections. An application deployed with an Active-Active database connects to a replica of the database that is geographically nearby. If that replica is not available, the application can failover to a remote replica, and failback again if necessary. In this article we explain how this process works.
Active-Active connection failover can improve data availability, but can negatively impact data consistency.</description></item></channel></rss>