<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Manage subscriptions on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rc/subscriptions/</link><description>Recent content in Manage subscriptions on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rc/subscriptions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create a Fixed subscription</title><link>/rc/subscriptions/create-fixed-subscription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/subscriptions/create-fixed-subscription/</guid><description>Fixed Size subscription plans support low throughput workflows. Several tiers are available, each designed for different memory sizes and integration requirements.
When creating your subscription, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to know which tier to choose.
(If you&amp;rsquo;re new to Redis Enterprise Cloud, the quick start helps you create an account with a free subscription and an initial database. You also learn how to connect to your database.)
Fixed plan subscription tiers Fixed plan pricing scales according to the memory size of all databases defined in the subscription.</description></item><item><title>Create a Flexible subscription</title><link>/rc/subscriptions/create-flexible-subscription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/subscriptions/create-flexible-subscription/</guid><description>Flexible subscriptions support any dataset size or throughput. Pricing is based on your workload requirements (database size and throughput.)
When you create a Flexible subscription, a cost estimate is provided to help you understand the impact of your requirements.
Create a Flexible subscription To create a Flexible subscription:
From the admin console menu, select the New Subscription button.
When the New subscription page appears, select Flexible plans and then scroll to the cloud vendor options.</description></item><item><title>Create an Active-Active subscription</title><link>/rc/subscriptions/create-active-active-subscription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/subscriptions/create-active-active-subscription/</guid><description>To deploy Active-Active databases in Redis Enterprise Cloud, you need to create a Flexible or Annual subscription with Active-Active enabled.
Overall, the process is similar to creating a traditional subscription. However, there are some differences; you need to:
Define the regions for each database instance Define unique CIDR addresses for each instance Define throughput (read and write operations) for each region Active-Active databases consist of multiple copies (also called instances) deployed to different regions throughout the world.</description></item><item><title>View or change a Fixed subscription</title><link>/rc/subscriptions/view-fixed-subscription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/subscriptions/view-fixed-subscription/</guid><description>To view the details of a Fixed subscription:
Sign in to the admin console.
If you have more than one subscription, select the target subscription from the subscription list.
Your subscription details appear, along with a summary of your database details.
From here, you can:
Select the Change Plan button to update the subscription plan tier, high availability settings, or payment method.
Select the New Database button to create a new database for your subscription.</description></item><item><title>View Flexible subscription details</title><link>/rc/subscriptions/view-flexible-subscription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/subscriptions/view-flexible-subscription/</guid><description>To view the details of a Flexible subscription:
Sign in to the admin console.
If you have more than one subscription, select the target subscription from the subscription list.
Your subscription details appear, along with a summary of your database details.
From here, you can:
Select the New database button to add a database to your subscription.
View the Status icon to learn the status of your subscription. Active subscriptions display a green circle with a check mark.</description></item><item><title>Delete a subscription</title><link>/rc/subscriptions/delete-subscription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/subscriptions/delete-subscription/</guid><description>To delete a subscription:
Delete all databases from the subscription.
The number of databases for the subscription is shown in the subscription list. You can not delete a subscription until there are zero databases in the subscription.
View the subscription details.
If you have more than one subscription, select the target subscription from the subscription list.
Select the Overview tab.
Locate and then select the Cancel subscription button near the bottom, right corner of the Overview details.</description></item></channel></rss>