<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Redis Stack and modules on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/modules/</link><description>Recent content in Redis Stack and modules on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/modules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Modules quick start</title><link>/modules/modules-quickstart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/modules-quickstart/</guid><description>To quickly set up a Redis database with modules, you can sign up for a free Redis Enterprise Cloud subscription and create a Redis Stack database.
Redis Stack databases include the following modules:
RediSearch RedisJSON RedisGraph RedisTimeSeries RedisBloom Alternatively, you can use one of these methods to set up a Redis database with modules:
Redis Enterprise Software Redis Enterprise Software in a Docker container Other platforms for Redis Enterprise Software Set up a Redis Cloud database To set up a Redis Cloud database with modules enabled, follow these steps:</description></item><item><title>Module lifecycle</title><link>/modules/modules-lifecycle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/modules-lifecycle/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software follows the Redis Enterprise lifecycle. (For complete details, see the Redis Enterprise Software subscription agreement.)
Redis modules also follow a release lifecycle and schedule. Here, you&amp;rsquo;ll find the &amp;ldquo;end-of-life&amp;rdquo; dates for each module and release.
Module release numbering Redis modules use a three-place numbering scheme to identify released versions.
The format is “Major1.Major2.Minor”.
Major sections of the version number represent fundamental changes to functionality and feature capabilities. The Major1 and Major2 part of the version number are incremented according to the size and scale of the changes in each release.</description></item><item><title>Enterprise feature compatibility for Redis modules</title><link>/modules/enterprise-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/enterprise-capabilities/</guid><description>This article describes Redis Enterprise feature compatibility for Redis modules. Version numbers indicate the minimum module version required for feature support. Footnotes provide additional information as needed.
Redis Enterprise module support The following table shows which modules are supported by Redis Enterprise Software and Redis Enterprise Cloud.
Module Redis EnterpriseSoftware Redis EnterpriseCloud RediSearch ✅ Yes ✅ Yes RedisJSON ✅ Yes ✅ Yes RedisGraph ✅ Yes ✅ Yes RedisTimeSeries ✅ Yes ✅ Yes RedisBloom ✅ Yes ✅ Yes RedisGears ✅ Yes ❌ No RedisAI ✅ Yes ❌ No Module feature support The following tables show feature support for each Redis module.</description></item><item><title>Redis Stack and Redis Enterprise</title><link>/modules/redis-stack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/redis-stack/</guid><description>Redis Stack simplifies installation and deployment of multiple modules with open source Redis databases.
Redis Enterprise Cloud and Redis Enterprise Software support all capabilities of Redis Stack.
For Fixed or Free subscriptions, Redis Enterprise Cloud supports Redis Stack through the Create database workflow.
When you create a new database in a Fixed or Free Redis Enterprise Cloud subscription, you can set the Type property to Redis Stack.
This automatically adds the following modules to the new database:</description></item></channel></rss>