<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BDB object on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb/</link><description>Recent content in BDB object on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BDB backup/export location object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb/backup_location/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb/backup_location/</guid><description>You can back up or export a database&amp;rsquo;s dataset to the following types of locations:
FTP/S SFTP Amazon S3 Google Cloud Storage Microsoft Azure Storage NAS/Local Storage Basic parameters For all backup/export location objects, you need to specify the location type via the type field.
Location type &amp;ldquo;type&amp;rdquo; value FTP/S &amp;ldquo;url&amp;rdquo; SFTP &amp;ldquo;sftp&amp;rdquo; Amazon S3 &amp;ldquo;s3&amp;rdquo; Google Cloud Storage &amp;ldquo;gs&amp;rdquo; Microsoft Azure Storage &amp;ldquo;abs&amp;rdquo; NAS/Local Storage &amp;ldquo;mount_point&amp;rdquo; Location-specific parameters Any additional required parameters may differ based on the backup/export location type.</description></item><item><title>BDB dataset import sources object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb/dataset_import_sources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb/dataset_import_sources/</guid><description>You can import data to a database from the following location types:
HTTP/S FTP SFTP Amazon S3 Google Cloud Storage Microsoft Azure Storage NAS/Local Storage The source file to import should be in the RDB format. It can also be in a compressed (gz) RDB file.
Supply an array of dataset import source objects to import data from multiple files.
Basic parameters For all import location objects, you need to specify the location type via the type field.</description></item><item><title>BDB replica sources status field</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb/replica_sources_status/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb/replica_sources_status/</guid><description>The replica_sources status field relates to the Replica Of feature, which enables the creation of a Redis database (single- or multi-shard) that synchronizes data from another Redis database (single- or multi-shard).
The status field represents the Replica Of sync status for a specific sync source.
Possible status values:
Status Description Possible next status &amp;lsquo;out-of-sync&amp;rsquo; Sync process is disconnected from source and trying to reconnect &amp;lsquo;syncing&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;syncing&amp;rsquo; Sync process is in progress &amp;lsquo;in-sync&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;out-of-sync&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;in-sync&amp;rsquo; Sync process finished successfully, and new commands are syncing on a regular basis &amp;lsquo;syncing&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;out-of-sync&amp;rsquo;</description></item><item><title>BDB replica sync field</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb/replica_sync/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb/replica_sync/</guid><description>The BDB replica_sync field relates to the Replica Of feature, which enables the creation of a Redis database (single- or multi-shard) that synchronizes data from another Redis database (single- or multi-shard).
You can use the replica_sync field to enable, disable, or pause the Replica Of sync process. The BDB crdt_sync field has a similar purpose for the Redis CRDB.
Possible BDB sync values:
Status Description Possible next status &amp;lsquo;disabled&amp;rsquo; (default value) Disables the sync process and represents that no sync is currently configured or running.</description></item><item><title>Snapshot policy object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb/snapshot_policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb/snapshot_policy/</guid><description> Name Type/Value Description secs integer Interval in seconds between snapshots writes integer Number of write changes required to trigger a snapshot</description></item><item><title>BDB status field</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb/status/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb/status/</guid><description>The BDB status field is a read-only field that represents the database status.
Possible status values:
Status Description Possible next status &amp;lsquo;active&amp;rsquo; Database is active and no special action is in progress &amp;lsquo;active-change-pending&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;import-pending&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;delete-pending&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;active-change-pending&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;active&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;creation-failed&amp;rsquo; Initial database creation failed &amp;lsquo;delete-pending&amp;rsquo; Database deletion is in progress &amp;lsquo;import-pending&amp;rsquo; Dataset import is in progress &amp;lsquo;active&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;pending&amp;rsquo; Temporary status during database creation &amp;lsquo;active&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;creation-failed&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;recovery&amp;rsquo; Not currently relevant (intended for future use)</description></item><item><title>Syncer sources object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb/syncer_sources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb/syncer_sources/</guid><description> Name Type/Value Description uid integer Unique ID of this source client_cert string Client certificate to use if encryption is enabled client_key string Client key to use if encryption is enabled compression integer, (range: 0-6) Compression level for the replication link encryption boolean Encryption enabled/disabled lag integer Lag in milliseconds between source and destination (while synced) last_error string Last error encountered when syncing from the source last_update string Time when we last received an update from the source rdb_size integer The source&amp;rsquo;s RDB size to be transferred during the syncing phase rdb_transferred integer Number of bytes transferred from the source&amp;rsquo;s RDB during the syncing phase replication_tls_sni string Replication TLS server name indication server_cert string Server certificate to use if encryption is enabled status string Sync status of this source uri string Source Redis URI</description></item></channel></rss>