<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rladmin node on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/node/</link><description>Recent content in rladmin node on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/node/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>rladmin node addr set</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/node/addr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/node/addr/</guid><description>Sets the internal IP address of a node. You can only set the internal IP address when the node is down.
rladmin node &amp;lt;ID&amp;gt; addr set &amp;lt;IP address&amp;gt; Parameters Parameter Type/Value Description node integer Sets the internal IP address of the specified node addr IP address Sets the node&amp;rsquo;s internal IP address to the specified IP address Returns Returns Updated successfully if the IP address was set. Otherwise, it returns an error.</description></item><item><title>rladmin node enslave</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/node/enslave/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/node/enslave/</guid><description>Changes the resources of a node to replicas.
node enslave Changes all of the node&amp;rsquo;s endpoints and shards to replicas.
rladmin node &amp;lt;ID&amp;gt; enslave [demote_node] [retry_timeout_seconds &amp;lt;seconds&amp;gt;] Parameters Parameter Type/Value Description node integer Changes all of the node&amp;rsquo;s endpoints and shards to replicas demote_node If the node is a primary node, changes the node to replica retry_timeout_seconds integer Retries on failure until the specified number of seconds has passed. Returns Returns OK if the roles were successfully changed.</description></item><item><title>rladmin node external_addr</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/node/external-addr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/node/external-addr/</guid><description>Configures a node&amp;rsquo;s external IP addresses.
node external_addr add Adds an external IP address that accepts inbound user connections for the node.
rladmin node &amp;lt;ID&amp;gt; external_addr add &amp;lt;IP address&amp;gt; Parameters Parameter Type/Value Description node integer Adds an external IP address for the specified node IP address IP address External IP address of the node Returns Returns Updated successfully if the IP address was added. Otherwise, it returns an error.
Use rladmin status nodes to verify the external IP address was added.</description></item><item><title>rladmin node maintenance_mode</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/node/maintenance-mode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/node/maintenance-mode/</guid><description>Configures quorum-only mode on a node.
node maintenance_mode on Migrates shards out of the node and turns the node into a quorum node to prevent shards from returning to it.
rladmin node &amp;lt;ID&amp;gt; maintenance_mode on [ keep_slave_shards ] [ demote_node ] [ max_concurrent_actions &amp;lt;integer&amp;gt; ] Parameters Parameter Type/Value Description node integer Turns the specified node into a quorum node demote_node If the node is a primary node, changes the node to replica keep_slave_shards Keeps replica shards in the node and demotes primary shards to replicas max_concurrent_actions integer Maximum number of concurrent actions during node maintenance Returns Returns OK if the node was converted successfully.</description></item><item><title>rladmin node recovery_path set</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/node/recovery-path/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/node/recovery-path/</guid><description>Sets the node&amp;rsquo;s local recovery path, which specifies the directory where persistence files are stored. You can use these persistence files to recover a failed database.
rladmin node &amp;lt;ID&amp;gt; recovery_path set &amp;lt;path&amp;gt; Parameters Parameter Type/Value Description node integer Sets the recovery path for the specified node path filepath Path to the folder where persistence files are stored Returns Returns Updated successfully if the recovery path was set. Otherwise, it returns an error.</description></item><item><title>rladmin node remove</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/node/remove/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/node/remove/</guid><description>Removes the specified node from the cluster.
rladmin node &amp;lt;ID&amp;gt; remove Parameters Parameter Type/Value Description node integer The node to remove from the cluster Returns Returns OK if the node was removed successfully. Otherwise, it returns an error.
Use rladmin status nodes to verify that the node was removed.
Example $ rladmin status nodes CLUSTER NODES: NODE:ID ROLE ADDRESS EXTERNAL_ADDRESS HOSTNAME SHARDS CORES FREE_RAM PROVISIONAL_RAM VERSION STATUS *node:1 master 192.0.2.12 198.</description></item><item><title>rladmin node snapshot</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/node/snapshot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/node/snapshot/</guid><description>Manages snapshots of the state of a node&amp;rsquo;s shards and endpoints.
node snapshot create Creates a snapshot of a node&amp;rsquo;s current state.
rladmin node &amp;lt;ID&amp;gt; snapshot create &amp;lt;name&amp;gt; Parameters Parameter Type/Value Description node integer Creates a snapshot of the specified node name string Name of the created snapshot Returns Returns Done if the snapshot was created successfully. Otherwise, returns an error.
Example $ rladmin node 1 snapshot create snap1 Creating node snapshot &amp;#39;snap1&amp;#39; for node:1 Done.</description></item></channel></rss>