<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>crdb-cli task commands on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/crdb-cli/task/</link><description>Recent content in crdb-cli task commands on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/references/cli-utilities/crdb-cli/task/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>crdb-cli task cancel</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/crdb-cli/task/cancel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/crdb-cli/task/cancel/</guid><description>Cancels the Active-Active database task specified by the task ID.
crdb-cli task cancel &amp;lt;task_id&amp;gt; Parameters Parameter Value Description task-id &amp;lt;task_id&amp;gt; string An Active-Active database task ID (required) Returns Attempts to cancel an Active-Active database task.
Be aware that tasks may complete before they can be cancelled.
Example $ crdb-cli task cancel --task-id 2901c2a3-2828-4717-80c0-6f27f1dd2d7c</description></item><item><title>crdb-cli task list</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/crdb-cli/task/list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/crdb-cli/task/list/</guid><description>Lists active and recent Active-Active database tasks.
crdb-cli task list Parameters None
Returns A table listing current and recent Active-Active tasks. Each entry includes the following:
Column Description Task ID String containing the unique ID associated with the taskExample: e1c49470-ae0b-4df8-885b-9c755dd614d0 CRDB-GUID String containing the unique ID associated with the Active-Active database affected by the taskExample: 1d7741cc-1110-4e2f-bc6c-935292783d24 Operation String describing the task actionExample: create_crdb Status String indicating the task statusExample: finished Worker name String identifying the process handling the taskExample: crdb_worker:1:0 Started TimeStamp value indicating when the task started (UTC)Example: 2022-10-12T09:33:41Z Ended TimeStamp value indicating when the task ended (UTC)Example: 2022-10-12T09:33:55Z Example $ crdb-cli task list TASK-ID CRDB-GUID OPERATION STATUS WORKER-NAME STARTED ENDED &amp;lt;task-ID&amp;gt; &amp;lt;crdb-ID&amp;gt; &amp;lt;operation&amp;gt; &amp;lt;result&amp;gt; &amp;lt;worker-ID&amp;gt; &amp;lt;started&amp;gt; &amp;lt;ended&amp;gt;</description></item><item><title>crdb-cli task status</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/crdb-cli/task/status/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/crdb-cli/task/status/</guid><description>Shows the status of a specified Active-Active database task.
crdb-cli task status --task-id &amp;lt;task_id&amp;gt; Parameters Parameter Value Description task-id &amp;lt;task_id&amp;gt; string An Active-Active database task ID (required) verbose N/A Returns detailed information when specified no-verbose N/A Returns limited information when specified The --verbose and --no-verbose options are mutually incompatible; specify one or the other.
The 404 Not Found error indicates an invalid task ID. Use the task list command to determine available task IDs.</description></item></channel></rss>