<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RedisGraph release notes on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/modules/redisgraph/release-notes/</link><description>Recent content in RedisGraph release notes on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/modules/redisgraph/release-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>RedisGraph 2.8 release notes</title><link>/modules/redisgraph/release-notes/redisgraph-2.8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/redisgraph/release-notes/redisgraph-2.8-release-notes/</guid><description>Requirements RedisGraph v2.8.24 requires:
Minimum Redis compatibility version (database): 6.2.0 Minimum Redis Enterprise Software version (cluster): 6.2.8 v2.8.24 (February 2023) This is a maintenance release for RedisGraph 2.8.
Update urgency: HIGH: There is a critical bug that may affect a subset of users. Upgrade!
Details:
Bug fixes:
#2777, #2841 Potential crash when sending queries from multiple connections and timeout is not 0 #2844 Potential partial results when same parametrized query is running from multiple connections #2739, #2774 Paths with exact variable length &amp;gt;1 are not matched Improvements:</description></item><item><title>RedisGraph 2.4 release notes</title><link>/modules/redisgraph/release-notes/redisgraph-2.4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/redisgraph/release-notes/redisgraph-2.4-release-notes/</guid><description>Requirements RedisGraph v2.4.14 requires:
Minimum Redis compatibility version (database): 6.0.0 Minimum Redis Enterprise Software version (cluster): 6.0.8 v2.4.14 (May 2022) This is a maintenance release for RedisGraph 2.4.
Update urgency: LOW: No need to upgrade unless there are new features you want to use.
Details:
Bug fixes:
#2072, #2081 CRLF sequences embedded in strings no longer trigger a protocol error when being emitted Improvements:
#2102 New load-time configuration option NODE_CREATION_BUFFER - see documentation (MOD-2348) Note: For Redis Enterprise users who want to upgrade to this patch, this version requires being on version 6.</description></item><item><title>RedisGraph 2.2 release notes</title><link>/modules/redisgraph/release-notes/redisgraph-2.2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/redisgraph/release-notes/redisgraph-2.2-release-notes/</guid><description>Requirements RedisGraph v2.2.16 requires:
Minimum Redis compatibility version (database): 5.0.7 Minimum Redis Enterprise Software version (cluster): 6.0.8 v2.2.16 (April 2021) This is a maintenance release for version 2.2.
Update urgency: Medium
Headlines:
This release improves overall stability and provides fixes for issues found after the previous release. Details:
Enhancements:
#1610 Add module-level configuration for query timeouts #1572 Remove query size limitation from parser #1590 Improve reporting of runtime errors #1596 Run bulk loader commands on a non-blocking thread Performance Improvements:</description></item><item><title>RedisGraph 2.0 release notes</title><link>/modules/redisgraph/release-notes/redisgraph-2.0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/redisgraph/release-notes/redisgraph-2.0-release-notes/</guid><description>Requirements RedisGraph v2.0.21 requires:
Minimum Redis compatibility version (database): 5.0.7 Minimum Redis Enterprise Software version (cluster): 5.4.11 v2.0.21 (October 2020) This is a maintenance release for version 2.0.
Headlines:
This release improves overall stability and provides fixes for issues found after the previous release. Details:
Minor enhancements:
#1326, #1330 Enable comments in Cypher queries. Bug fixes:
#1338 Update parser to support negative values.
#1319 Replace assertion with runtime error - execution plan building process is unable locate an operation suitable for a filter.</description></item><item><title>RedisGraph 1.2 release notes</title><link>/modules/redisgraph/release-notes/redisgraph-1.2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/redisgraph/release-notes/redisgraph-1.2-release-notes/</guid><description>Requirements RedisGraph v1.2.2 requires:
Minimum Redis compatibility version (database): 4.0.0 Minimum Redis Enterprise Software version (cluster): 5.0.0 v1.2.2 (May 2019) Update urgency: Medium This is a maintenance release for version 1.2.
This release improves overall stability and provides fixes for issues found after the previous release.
v1.2.0 (April 2019) This is a major release for RedisGraph. Compared to previous release 1.0.15:
Added functionality #452 Support multiple relationships of the same type R connecting two nodes #392 Lexer elides escape characters in string creation: support for property values with ' or &amp;quot; Performance improvements #442 Seek graph entity by id: MATCH (n) WHERE ID(n) = 5 RETURN n #422 MATCH (n) RETURN COUNT(n) is now O(1) #421 and #459 Lazy loading of matrices on subsequent writes of relationships and nodes #399 Single transpose of matrices Minor Bugfixes: #456 Memory leaks #439 When label doesn&amp;rsquo;t exists, the node count should return 0 #439 #435 Referencing non existing properties #435 Compared to 1.</description></item><item><title>RedisGraph 1.0 release notes</title><link>/modules/redisgraph/release-notes/redisgraph-1.0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/redisgraph/release-notes/redisgraph-1.0-release-notes/</guid><description>Requirements RedisGraph v1.0.15 requires:
Minimum Redis compatibility version (database): 4.0.0 Minimum Redis Enterprise Software version (cluster): 5.0.0 v1.0.15 (March 2019) GraphBLAS 2.3.0 release notes WITH clause: Allows query parts to be chained together, piping the results from one to be used as starting points or criteria of the next. ref p.78 Enhancements #393 Discard distinct when performing aggregation Minor bugfixes #359 Adding ORDER BY changes the number of returned hits when used in combination with LIMIT #363 Remove graph entity property when it is set to null #386 Return updated values on queries that modify data v1.</description></item></channel></rss>