<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Manage databases on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rc/databases/</link><description>Recent content in Manage databases on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rc/databases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Active-Active Redis</title><link>/rc/databases/active-active-redis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/databases/active-active-redis/</guid><description>Active-Active databases store data across multiple regions and availability zones. This improves scalability, performance, and availability, especially when compared to standalone databases. To create Active-Active databases, you need a Flexible (or Annual) Redis Enterprise Cloud subscription that enables Active-Active Redis and defines the regions for each copy of your databases. This is defined when you create a new subscription.
Active-Active databases are distributed across multiple regions (geo-distribution). This improves performance by reducing latency for nearby users and improves availability by protecting against data loss in case of network or resource failure.</description></item><item><title>Create a database</title><link>/rc/databases/create-database/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/databases/create-database/</guid><description>To create a database in your Redis Enterprise Cloud subscription:
Sign in to the Redis Cloud admin portal. (Create an account if you don&amp;rsquo;t already have one.)
If you have more than one subscription, select the target subscription from the list. This displays the Databases tab for the selected subscription.
Select the New database button.
This displays the New database screen, which varies according to your subscription plan.
The New database screen is divided into sections, each dedicated to a specific category of settings.</description></item><item><title>View and edit databases</title><link>/rc/databases/view-edit-database/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/databases/view-edit-database/</guid><description>Use the Databases menu of the admin console to manage your subscription databases.
To view the details of a database:
Sign in to the Redis Cloud admin console. (Create an account if you don&amp;rsquo;t already have one.)
Locate the database in the list.
Select the database name to open the Database page.
The Database screen lets you review:
Configuration details of a database Graphs showing performance metrics Recent activity via a &amp;ldquo;slowlog,&amp;rdquo; which lists queries that exceed a certain execution time.</description></item><item><title>Delete database</title><link>/rc/databases/delete-database/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/databases/delete-database/</guid><description>To delete a database, use the Delete button. It&amp;rsquo;s located in the Danger zone section of the database&amp;rsquo;s Configuration tab.
Databases must be empty before they can be deleted. Deleted databases cannot be recovered. (We recommend making a backup, just in case.)
This command requires the account owner role.
Step-by-step Sign in to the Redis Cloud admin portal.
If you have more than one subscription, select the target subscription from the list.</description></item><item><title>Back up a database</title><link>/rc/databases/back-up-data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/databases/back-up-data/</guid><description>The backup options for Redis Enterprise Cloud databases depend on your plan:
Flexible and Annual subscriptions can perform backups on-demand and schedule daily backups that occur during a set hour.
Paid Fixed plans can perform backups on-demand and schedule backups that occur every 24 hours.
Free plans cannot perform backups through the Redis Cloud console.
Backups are saved to predefined storage locations available to your subscription.
Backup locations need to be available before you turn on database backups.</description></item><item><title>Flush data</title><link>/rc/databases/flush-data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/databases/flush-data/</guid><description>The FLUSHALL command provides a fast way to remove all data from a database.
To use it, connect your database and then issue the command.
There are several ways to do this, depending on your circumstances and environment.
Note: When you flush a database, you remove all data. This is a prerequisite to deleting a database.
This permanently removes all data from the database. The data cannot be recovered, except by restoring from earlier backups.</description></item><item><title>Import data into a database</title><link>/rc/databases/import-data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/databases/import-data/</guid><description>You can import an existing dataset into your Redis Cloud instance from an existing Redis server or an RDB file.
Note: Expired keys are not imported. As a result, the number of keys in the source and destination databases can be different after the import is complete. Import from a Redis server To import a dataset from any publicly available Redis server:
Select Databases from the admin console menu and then select the target database from the database list.</description></item><item><title>Migrate data to new subscription</title><link>/rc/databases/migrate-databases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/databases/migrate-databases/</guid><description>There are times when you need to migrate data from one database to another.
Here are two common ways to do this.
Each approach is suitable for different situations and the steps can vary according to your needs.
Transfer via import The most common way to transfer data to a new database is to import a copy of the data into it.
Here&amp;rsquo;s how it works:
Select an export storage destination and verify that it&amp;rsquo;s ready for use and has sufficient space.</description></item><item><title>Monitor database performance</title><link>/rc/databases/monitor-performance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/databases/monitor-performance/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Cloud provides a variety of metrics to help you monitor database performance. You can view graphs of performance data at any time and receive emails when performance crosses defined threshholds.
View database metrics The Metrics tab of the View Database screen provides a series of graphs showing performance data for your database.
Performance data provides insight into how your database is being used and how well it is performing.</description></item><item><title>System logs</title><link>/rc/databases/system-logs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/databases/system-logs/</guid><description>The Logs page contains events, alerts, and logs from the activities, databases, and subscriptions associated with your account.
You can:
Sort the list by a specific field in descending or ascending order. Supported fields include Time, Originator, Database name, and Activity.
Select the arrow icon to change the sort order. You can only sort by one field at a time.
Use the Export all button to export all logs as a comma-separated values (CSV) file for use in other systems and programs.</description></item><item><title>Usage reports</title><link>/rc/databases/usage-reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/databases/usage-reports/</guid><description>The Usage Report shows the daily memory usage and shard usage of all databases from the subscriptions associated with your account.
To filter the data, you can:
Select a month and year from the View Statement For list to view the daily memory usage during a specific month. Select a subscription from the Subscription list to view the daily memory usage of a specific subscription associated with your account. Select a database from the Database list to view the daily memory usage of a specific database.</description></item></channel></rss>