<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Install and setup on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/</link><description>Recent content in Install and setup on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/installing-upgrading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Get started with Redis Enterprise Software</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/get-started-redis-enterprise-software/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/get-started-redis-enterprise-software/</guid><description>This guide helps you install Redis Enterprise Software on a Linux host to test its capabilities.
When finished, you&amp;rsquo;ll have a simple cluster with a single node:
Step 1: Install Redis Enterprise Software Step 2: Set up a Redis Enterprise Software cluster Step 3: Create a new Redis database Step 4: Connect to your Redis database Note: This quick start is designed for local testing only. For production environments, the install and setup guide walks through deployment options appropriate for a production environment.</description></item><item><title>Get started with Redis Enterprise Software using Docker</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/get-started-docker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/get-started-docker/</guid><description>Warning - Docker containers are currently only supported for development and testing environments, not for production. For testing purposes, you can run Redis Enterprise Software (RS) on Docker containers on Linux, Windows, or MacOS. The Redis Enterprise Software container represents a node in an RS Cluster. When deploying RS using Docker, there are a couple of common topologies:
Topology #1: The simplest topology is to run a single-node RS Cluster with a single container in a single host machine.</description></item><item><title>Supported platforms</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/supported-platforms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/supported-platforms/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software is supported on several operating systems, cloud environments, and virtual environments.
System requirements Make sure your system meets these requirements:
Only 64-bit operating systems are supported. You must install Redis Enterprise Software directly on the host, not through system cloning. You must install on a clean host with no other applications running so that all RAM is allocated to the operating system and Redis Enterprise Software only.</description></item><item><title>File locations</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/file-locations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/file-locations/</guid><description>To make sure that Redis Enterprise Software functions properly, make sure that you handle the files in the application directories with care.
Application directories The directories that Redis Enterprise Software installs into are:
Path Description /opt/redislabs Main installation directory for all Redis Enterprise Software binaries /opt/redislabs/bin Binaries for all the utilities for command line access and managements such as &amp;ldquo;rladmin&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;redis-cli&amp;rdquo; /opt/redislabs/config System configuration files /opt/redislabs/lib System library files /opt/redislabs/sbin System binaries for tweaking provisioning Configuration and data directories The default directories that Redis Enterprise Software uses for data and metadata are:</description></item><item><title>Customize installation directories</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/customize-install-directories/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/customize-install-directories/</guid><description>When installing Redis Enterprise Software, you can customize the installation directories.
The files are installed in the redislabs directory located in the path that you specify.
Note: Custom installation directories are supported on RedHat Enterprise Linux version 7 and 8. When you install with custom directories, the installation does not run as an RPM file. If a redislabs directory already exists in the path that you specify, the installation fails. All nodes in a cluster must be installed with the same file locations.</description></item><item><title>Customize system user and group</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/customize-user-and-group/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/customize-user-and-group/</guid><description>By default, Redis Enterprise Software is installed with the user:group redislabs:redislabs.
During the installation, you can specify the user and group that own all Redis Enterprise Software processes.
If you specify the user only, then installation is run with the primary group that the user belongs to.
Note: Custom installation user is supported on RedHat Enterprise Linux. When you install with custom directories, the installation does not run as an RPM file.</description></item><item><title>Manage installation questions</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/manage-installation-questions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/manage-installation-questions/</guid><description>Several questions are displayed during the Redis Software installation process.
Here, you&amp;rsquo;ll find a list of these questions and learn how to automatically answer these questions to perform a silent install.
Installation questions Several questions appear during installation:
Linux swap file - Swap is enabled. Do you want to proceed? [Y/N]?
We recommend that you disable Linux swap in the operating system configuration to give Redis Software control of the memory allocation.</description></item><item><title>Offline Installation</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/offline-installation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/offline-installation/</guid><description>By default, the installation process requires an Internet connection to enable installing dependency packages and for synchronizing the operating system clock against an NTP server.
If you install Redis Enterprise Software (RS) on a machine with no Internet connection, you need to perform these two tasks manually, as follows:
First, you need to install the required dependency packages. When RS is installed on a machine that is not connected to the Internet, the installation process fails and displays an error message informing you it failed to automatically install dependencies.</description></item><item><title>Upgrade an existing Redis Enterprise Software deployment</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/upgrading/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/upgrading/</guid><description>To upgrade Redis Enterprise Software, you:
Upgrade the software on all nodes of the cluster.
(Optional) Upgrade each database in the cluster.
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to upgrade the databases in your cluster; however, new features and important fixes might not be enabled until you do so.
Default Redis database versions When you upgrade an existing database or create a new one, it uses the default Redis version (default_redis_version) unless you specify the database version explicitly with redis_version in the REST API or rladmin upgrade db.</description></item><item><title>Uninstall Redis Enterprise Software</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/uninstalling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/uninstalling/</guid><description>Use the rl_uninstall script to uninstall Redis Enterprise Software and remove its files.
sudo ./rl_uninstall.sh By default, the script is located in /opt/redislabs/bin.</description></item><item><title>Redis Enterprise Software product lifecycle</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/product-lifecycle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/product-lifecycle/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software product lifecycle fully reflects our subscription agreement. However, for any discrepancy between the two policies, the subscription agreement prevails.
Redis Enterprise modules follow the modules lifecycle.
Release numbers Redis uses a four-place numbering scheme to designate released versions of its products. The format is “Major1.Major2.Minor-Build”.
Major sections of the version number represents fundamental changes and additions in capabilities to Redis Enterprise Software. The Major1 and Major2 part of the version number are incremented based on the size and scale of the changes in each release.</description></item><item><title>Creating a Support Package</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/creating-support-package/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/creating-support-package/</guid><description>If you encounter any issues that you are not able to resolve yourself and need to contact Redis support for assistance, you can create a support package that gathers all essential information to help us debug your issues.
Note: The process of creating the support package can take several minutes and generates load on the system. Creating a support package To create a support package:
Click Support at the top right of the admin console.</description></item><item><title>Hardware requirements</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/hardware-requirements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/hardware-requirements/</guid><description>The hardware requirements for Redis Enterprise Software are different for development and production environments.
In a development environment, you can test your application with a live database.
If you want to test your application under production conditions, use the production environment requirements.
In a production environment you must have enough resources to handle the load on the database and recover from failures.
Development environment You can build your development environment with non-production hardware, such as a laptop, desktop, or small VM or instance, and with these hardware requirements:</description></item><item><title>Node persistent and ephemeral storage</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/persistent-ephemeral-storage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/persistent-ephemeral-storage/</guid><description>For each node in the cluster, you can configure both persistent storage and ephemeral storage paths.
Persistent storage is mandatory. It is used by the cluster to store information that needs to persist even if a shard or a node fails, including server logs, configurations, files. For example, if you configure persistence for a database, then the persistence information is stored in this location.
The persistent volume must be a SAN (Storage Area Network) using an EXT4 or XFS file system and be connected as an external storage volume.</description></item></channel></rss>