<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Installation on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/ri/installing/</link><description>Recent content in Installation on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/ri/installing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Install the RedisInsight Desktop Client</title><link>/ri/installing/install-redis-desktop/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 03:49:29 +0530</pubDate><guid>/ri/installing/install-redis-desktop/</guid><description>The RedisInsight desktop client allows you to download and use the RedisInsight UI locally. The desktop client is supported on Windows, MacOS, and Ubuntu operating systems and works with all variants of Redis.
System Requirements Requirement Ubuntu MacOS Windows Operating System Ubuntu 18.04 LTS or later MacOS 10.13 or later Windows 10 Memory (RAM) 8GB 8GB 8GB Processor 64 bit 64 bit 32 bit or 64 bit Note: For unsupported operating systems, you can still install RedisInsight.</description></item><item><title>Install RedisInsight on Docker</title><link>/ri/installing/install-docker/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 03:49:29 +0530</pubDate><guid>/ri/installing/install-docker/</guid><description>This tutorial shows how to install RedisInsight on Docker so you can use RedisInsight in development. See a separate guide for installing RedisInsight on AWS.
Install Docker The first step is to install Docker for your operating system. On Windows and Mac, install Docker version 18.03 or higher. To check which Docker version you have, run docker version.
Run RedisInsight Docker image Next, run the RedisInsight container.
docker run -v redisinsight:/db -p 8001:8001 redislabs/redisinsight:latest Then, point your browser to http://localhost:8001.</description></item><item><title>Install RedisInsight on Kubernetes</title><link>/ri/installing/install-k8s/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 03:49:29 +0530</pubDate><guid>/ri/installing/install-k8s/</guid><description>In this walkthrough, we will install RedisInsight on Kubernetes. This is an easy way to use RedisInsight with a Redis Enterprise K8s deployment.
Create the RedisInsight deployment and service Below is an annotated YAML file that will create a RedisInsight deployment and a service in a k8s cluster.
Create a new file redisinsight.yaml with the content below # RedisInsight service with name &amp;#39;redisinsight-service&amp;#39; apiVersion: v1 kind: Service metadata: name: redisinsight-service # name should not be &amp;#39;redisinsight&amp;#39; # since the service creates # environment variables that # conflicts with redisinsight # application&amp;#39;s environment # variables `REDISINSIGHT_HOST` and # `REDISINSIGHT_PORT` spec: type: LoadBalancer ports: - port: 80 targetPort: 8001 selector: app: redisinsight --- # RedisInsight deployment with name &amp;#39;redisinsight&amp;#39; apiVersion: apps/v1 kind: Deployment metadata: name: redisinsight #deployment name labels: app: redisinsight #deployment label spec: replicas: 1 #a single replica pod selector: matchLabels: app: redisinsight #which pods is the deployment managing, as defined by the pod template template: #pod template metadata: labels: app: redisinsight #label for pod/s spec: containers: - name: redisinsight #Container name (DNS_LABEL, unique) image: redislabs/redisinsight:latest #repo/image imagePullPolicy: IfNotPresent #Always pull image volumeMounts: - name: db #Pod volumes to mount into the container&amp;#39;s filesystem.</description></item><item><title>Install RedisInsight on AWS EC2</title><link>/ri/installing/install-ec2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 03:49:29 +0530</pubDate><guid>/ri/installing/install-ec2/</guid><description>This tutorial shows how to install RedisInsight on an AWS EC2 instance and manage ElastiCache Redis instances using RedisInsight. To complete this tutorial you must have access to the AWS Console and permissions to launch EC2 instances.
Step 1: Create a new IAM Role (Optional) RedisInsight needs read-only access to S3 and ElastiCache APIs. This is an optional step.
Login to AWS Console, and navigate to IAM screen Create a new IAM Role Under Select type of trusted entity, choose EC2.</description></item><item><title>Configure RedisInsight</title><link>/ri/installing/configurations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 03:49:29 +0530</pubDate><guid>/ri/installing/configurations/</guid><description>You can configure RedisInsight with system environment variables.
To configure RedisInsight with environment variables:
Follow the instructions to set environment variables for your operating system:
Mac Windows Linux Docker Set the environment variables.
Restart RedisInsight.
RedisInsight environment variables The following environment variables can be set to configure RedisInsight:
RIPORT Description: Which port should RedisInsight listen on.
Type: Number
Default: 8001
RIHOST Description: Which host should RedisInsight bind to.
Type: String</description></item></channel></rss>