<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data types for Active-Active databases on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/data-types/</link><description>Recent content in Data types for Active-Active databases on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/databases/active-active/develop/data-types/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hashes in an Active-Active databases</title><link>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/data-types/hashes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/data-types/hashes/</guid><description>Hashes are great for structured data that contain a map of fields and values. They are used for managing distributed user or app session state, user preferences, form data and so on. Hash fields contain string type and string types operate just like the standard Redis string types when it comes to CRDTs. Fields in hashes can be initialized as a string using HSET or HMSET or can be used to initialize counter types that are numeric integers using HINCRBY or floats using HINCRBYFLOAT.</description></item><item><title>HyperLogLog in Active-Active databases</title><link>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/data-types/hyperloglog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/data-types/hyperloglog/</guid><description>HyperLogLog is an algorithm that addresses the count-distinct problem. To do this it approximates the numbers of items in a set. Determining the exact cardinality of a set requires memory according to the cardinality of the set. Because it estimates the cardinality by probability, the HyperLogLog algorithm can run with more reasonable memory requirements.
HyperLogLog in Redis Open source Redis implements HyperLogLog (HLL) as a native data-structure. It supports adding elements (PFADD) to an HLL, counting elements (PFCOUNT) of HLLs, and merging of (PFMERGE) HLLs.</description></item><item><title>Lists in Active-Active databases</title><link>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/data-types/lists/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/data-types/lists/</guid><description>Redis lists are simply lists of strings, sorted by insertion order. It is possible to add elements to a Redis List that push new elements to the head (on the left) or to the tail (on the right) of the list. Redis lists can be used to easily implement queues (using LPUSH and RPOP, for example) and stacks (using LPUSH and LPOP, for example).
Lists in Active-Active databases are just the same as regular Redis Lists.</description></item><item><title>Sets in Active-Active databases</title><link>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/data-types/sets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/data-types/sets/</guid><description>A Redis set is an unordered collection of strings. It is possible to add, remove, and test for the existence of members with Redis commands. A Redis set maintains a unique collection of elements. Sets can be great for maintaining a list of events (click streams), users (in a group conversation), products (in recommendation lists), engagements (likes, shares) and so on.
Sets in Active-Active databases behave the same and maintain additional metadata to achieve an &amp;ldquo;OR-Set&amp;rdquo; behavior to handle concurrent conflicting writes.</description></item><item><title>Sorted sets in Active-Active databases</title><link>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/data-types/sorted-sets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/data-types/sorted-sets/</guid><description>Note: Redis Geospatial (Geo) is based on Sorted Sets, so the same Active-Active database development instructions apply to Geo. Similar to Redis Sets, Redis Sorted Sets are non-repeating collections of Strings. The difference between the two is that every member of a Sorted Set is associated with a score used to order the Sorted Set from lowest to highest. While members are unique, they may have the same score.</description></item><item><title>Streams in Active-Active databases</title><link>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/data-types/streams/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/data-types/streams/</guid><description>A Redis Stream is a data structure that acts like an append-only log. Each stream entry consists of:
A unique, monotonically increasing ID A payload consisting of a series key-value pairs You add entries to a stream with the XADD command. You access stream entries using the XRANGE, XREADGROUP, and XREAD commands (however, see the caveat about XREAD below).
Streams and Active-Active Active-Active databases allow you to write to the same logical stream from more than one region.</description></item><item><title>Strings and bitfields in Active-Active databases</title><link>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/data-types/strings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/databases/active-active/develop/data-types/strings/</guid><description>Active-Active databases support both strings and bitfields.
Note: Active-Active bitfield support was added in RS version 6.0.20. Changes to both of these data structures will be replicated across Active-Active member databases.
Replication semantics Except in the case of string counters (see below), both strings and bitfields are replicated using a &amp;ldquo;last write wins&amp;rdquo; approach. The reason for this is that strings and bitfields are effectively binary objects. So, unlike with lists, sets, and hashes, the conflict resolution semantics of a given operation on a string or bitfield are undefined.</description></item></channel></rss>