<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release notes on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/release-notes/</link><description>Recent content in Release notes on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/release-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Redis Enterprise Software release notes 6.4.2 (February 2023)</title><link>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-4-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-4-2/</guid><description>​​Redis Enterprise Software version 6.4.2 is now available!
The following table shows the MD5 checksums for the available packages:
Package MD5 checksum (6.4.2 February release) Ubuntu 16 b0dbecaa974ca08245dda55d53b6fe9b Ubuntu 18 a5192e8b0734db80d6b7c2b98a170c58 RedHat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 7Oracle Enterprise Linux (OL) 7 c1537855dcfe7a7cedf9031ce01e2b9b RedHat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 8Oracle Enterprise Linux (OL) 8 Rocky Enterprise Linux a24dc749d6dcb5df2162d7a41791c7aa This version offers:
Extended validation of client certificates via mTLS (mutual TLS) full subject support
Support for default restrictive permissions when using publish/subscribe commands and ACLs (access control lists)</description></item><item><title>Redis Enterprise Software release notes 6.2.18 (September 2022)</title><link>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-2-18/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-2-18/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software version 6.2.18 is now available!
This version of Redis Enterprise Software offers:
RedisJSON on Active-Active General Availability Database connection auditing Private key encryption Active-Active support for memory usage command crdb-cli improvements Compatibility with open source Redis v6.2.6 Additional enhancements and fixes The following table shows the MD5 checksums for the available packages:
Package MD5 Checksum (6.2.18-70 January release) Ubuntu 16 69d2d2c71232adb15cebf29308ac54da Ubuntu 18 22e0637107a32ccb96a704abe9650adf RedHat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 7Oracle Enterprise Linux (OL) 7 e14fcf6973418602f2b64a55a0bc8374 RedHat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 8Oracle Enterprise Linux (OL) 8 Rocky Enterprise Linux f61d0d8f0bb5ad90a470482d6575eb27 Features and enhancements General Availability of Active-Active databases with RedisJSON Active-Active databases now support Index, query, and full-text search of nested JSON documents when combining RedisJSON with RediSearch.</description></item><item><title>Redis Enterprise Software release notes 6.2.12 (August 2022)</title><link>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-2-12/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-2-12/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software version 6.2.12 is now available!
This version of Redis Enterprise Software offers:
OCSP stapling of the server proxy certificate Password and session configuration settings via the admin console Compatibility with open source Redis v6.2.6 Support for Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) v8.6 Additional enhancements and fixes The following table shows the MD5 checksums for the available packages.
Package MD5 Checksum Ubuntu 16 e702c906f200940e06ef031e6b8006d9 Ubuntu 18 7ea70067e8828b59336380df087fe03d RedHat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 7Oracle Enterprise Linux (OL) 7 8ffda6186f70354b9d10c1ce43938c3c RedHat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 8Oracle Enterprise Linux (OL) 8 334fe7979a7376b28fcf48913403bfb7 Features and enhancements Server side OCSP Stapling</description></item><item><title>Redis Enterprise Software Release Notes 6.2.10 (February 2022)</title><link>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-2-10-february-2022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-2-10-february-2022/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software version 6.2.10 is now available!
The following table shows the MD5 checksums for the available packages.
Package MD5 Checksum Ubuntu 16 531cea69a58fbc1125bc5f76ba01da7f Ubuntu 18 ec9ac6e0111dc85605d3b98e83f50150 RedHat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 7Oracle Enterprise Linux (OL) 7 2f7572caab9600417ef8b4ee474d6768 RedHat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 8Oracle Enterprise Linux (OL) 8 377a539ee050515e1e0640dec1e04129 K8s Ubuntu 099192416a70a12790535bdcd78a6e87 K8s RHEL f267abe81770ddf36f022232f4c2cb2e Features and enhancements Upgrade the Redis Enterprise infrastructure to Python v3.9.
Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) v8.</description></item><item><title>Redis Enterprise Software Release Notes 6.2.8 (October 2021)</title><link>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-2-8-october-2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-2-8-october-2021/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software version 6.2.8 is now available!
Features and enhancements This version features:
Support for Red Hat Linux Edition (RHEL) 8 You can now set the start time for 12- and 24-hour backups Compatibility with version of open source Redis 6.2.3 (starting with Redis Enterprise Software v6.2.4) Compatibility with the security fixes of the latest open source Redis 6.2.6 Enhancements and bug fixes Version changes Prerequisites and notes You can upgrade to v6.</description></item><item><title>Redis Enterprise Software Release Notes 6.2.4 (August 2021)</title><link>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-2-4-august-2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-2-4-august-2021/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software version 6.2.4 is now available!
This version offers:
Encryption of all communications within cluster nodes Security enhancements Bug fixes Compatibility with the latest version of open source Redis 6.2.3 Version changes Prerequisites and notes You can upgrade to v6.2.4 from Redis Enterprise Software v6.0 and later.
Keep the following in mind:
Upgrades from versions earlier than v6.0 are not supported
The new internode encryption feature requires port 3342 to be open on all machines in the cluster.</description></item><item><title>Redis Enterprise Software Release Notes 6.0.20 (April 2021)</title><link>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-0-20-april-2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-0-20-april-2021/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software version 6.0.20 is now available! This version includes the following new features and improvements:
A new integration for LDAP authentication and authorization into RS role-based access controls (RBAC). You can now use LDAP to authorize access to the admin console and to authorize database access.
An enhanced clients mutual authentication mechanism, adding the ability to authenticate client connections using a Certificate Authority (CA).
Support of Redis eviction policies on Active-Active Redis databases.</description></item><item><title>Redis Enterprise Software Release Notes 6.0.12 (January 2021)</title><link>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-0-12-january-2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-0-12-january-2021/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software (RS) 6.0.12 is now available! This version includes the following new features and improvements:
Synchronization can now be distributed across the nodes of Active-Active or Active-Passive databases You can disable several internal RS services to free up more memory User accounts can have multiple passwords to allow for password rotation Dependencies are automatically installed when you add modules to a cluster Envoy replaces NGINX for internal cluster administration Automatic recovery of the syncer processs from out-of-memory (preview mode) And other functional and stability improvements.</description></item><item><title>Redis Enterprise Software Release Notes 6.0.8 (September 2020)</title><link>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-0-8-september-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-0-8-september-2020/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software (RS) 6.0.8 is now available! This version includes the new RediSearch 2.0 module, open source Redis 6.0.5, changes the rladmin tool for upgrading modules, and includes bug fixes.
Version information Upgrade instructions Follow these instructions for upgrading to RS 6.0.8 from RS 5.4.0 and above. For Active-Active deployments, this release requires that you upgrade the CRDB featureset version.
End of life End of Life (EOL) for Redis Enterprise Software 6.</description></item><item><title>Redis Enterprise Software Release Notes 6.0 (May 2020)</title><link>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-0-may-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/release-notes/rs-6-0-may-2020/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software (RS) 6.0 is now available! This new version bundles open-source Redis 6, implements enhanced Access Control List (ACL) capabilities using Role-Based Access Control (RBAC) for database access, and adds the support of Redis Streams on Active-Active databases.
Version information Upgrade instructions Follow these instructions for upgrading to RS 6.0 from RS 5.4.0 and above. For Active-Active deployments, this release requires that you upgrade the CRDB featureset version.</description></item><item><title>Redis Enterprise Software Release Notes 5.6.0 (April 2020)</title><link>/rs/release-notes/rs-5-6-0-april-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/release-notes/rs-5-6-0-april-2020/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software (RS) 5.6.0 is now available. This major version release includes:
Improved installation process to be customizable Support for the HyperLogLog data type in Active-Active databases RedisJSON support in Redis on Flash databases Support for Redis OSS Cluster API for Active-Active and Replica Of databases Replica HA enabled by default for Active-Active databases Cloud backup locations support Support for Red Hat Enterprise Linux version 7.7, 7.8 Additional enhancements, and minor bug fixes Information Upgrade Follow these instructions for upgrading to RS 5.</description></item><item><title>Redis Enterprise Software Release Notes 5.5 Preview (April 2019)</title><link>/rs/release-notes/rs-5-5-preview-april-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/release-notes/rs-5-5-preview-april-2019/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software (RS) 5.5 Preview Edition is now available.
RS 5.5 is a preview version that includes all the capabilities of Redis Enterprise 5.4, plus support for creation of Redis databases with multiple modules and support for these modules:
RediSearch (GA) RedisGraph (GA) RedisBloom (GA) RedisJSON (GA) RedisAI (Preview Version) RedisTimeSeries (Preview Version) RedisGears (Preview Version) New features RS 5.5 lets you create Redis databases with multiple Redis modules.</description></item></channel></rss>