<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Certificates on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/security/certificates/</link><description>Recent content in Certificates on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/security/certificates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create certificates</title><link>/rs/security/certificates/create-certificates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/certificates/create-certificates/</guid><description>Follow these instructions to create your own certificates to install on your Redis Enterprise cluster. Note that you can install a separate certificate per cluster component.
Create a private key:
openssl genrsa -out &amp;lt;key-file-name&amp;gt;.pem 2048 Create a certificate signing request:
openssl req -new -key &amp;lt;key-file-name&amp;gt;.pem -out &amp;lt;key-file-name&amp;gt;.csr Note: You will be prompted for a Country Name, State or Province Name, Locality Name, Organization Name, Organizational Unit, and Common Name.
You will need to check with your security team or certificate authority for the right values for your organization.</description></item><item><title>Update certificates</title><link>/rs/security/certificates/updating-certificates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/certificates/updating-certificates/</guid><description>Warning - When you update the certificates, the new certificate replaces the same certificates on all nodes in the cluster. How to update certificates You can use either the rladmin command-line interface (CLI) or the REST API to update certificates.
The new certificates are used the next time the clients connect to the database.
When you upgrade Redis Enterprise Software, the upgrade process copies the certificates that are on the first upgraded node to all of the nodes in the cluster.</description></item><item><title>Enable OCSP stapling</title><link>/rs/security/certificates/ocsp-stapling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/certificates/ocsp-stapling/</guid><description>OCSP (Online Certificate Status Protocol) lets a client or server verify the status (GOOD, REVOKED, or UNKNOWN) of a certificate maintained by a third-party certificate authority (CA).
To check whether a certificate is still valid or has been revoked, a client or server can send a request to the CA&amp;rsquo;s OCSP server (also called an OCSP responder). The OCSP responder checks the certificate&amp;rsquo;s status in the CA&amp;rsquo;s certificate revocation list and sends the status back as a signed and timestamped response.</description></item></channel></rss>