<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Manage clusters on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/clusters/</link><description>Recent content in Manage clusters on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/clusters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Set up a new cluster</title><link>/rs/clusters/new-cluster-setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/clusters/new-cluster-setup/</guid><description>A Redis Enterprise Software cluster typically consists of several nodes. For production deployments, we recommend an uneven number of nodes, with a minimum of three.
Note: In a cluster that consists of only one node, some features and capabilities are not enabled, such as database replication that provides high availability. To set up a new cluster, you must first install the Redis Enterprise Software package and then set up the cluster as described below.</description></item><item><title>Add a cluster node</title><link>/rs/clusters/add-node/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/clusters/add-node/</guid><description>When you install Redis Enterprise Software on the first node of a cluster, you create the new cluster. After you install the first node, you can add more nodes to the cluster.
Note: Before you add a node to the cluster:
The clocks on all nodes must always be synchronized.
If the clock in the node you are trying to join to the cluster is not synchronized with the nodes already in the cluster, the action fails and an error message is shown indicating that you must synchronize the clocks first.</description></item><item><title>Maintenance mode for cluster nodes</title><link>/rs/clusters/maintenance-mode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/clusters/maintenance-mode/</guid><description>Use maintenance mode to prevent data loss during hardware or operating system maintenance on Redis Enterprise servers. When maintenance mode is on, all shards move off of the node under maintenance and migrate to another available node.
Activate maintenance mode When you activate maintenance mode, Redis Enterprise does the following:
Checks whether a shut down of the node will cause quorum loss. If so, maintenance mode will not turn on.</description></item><item><title>Recover a failed cluster</title><link>/rs/clusters/cluster-recovery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/clusters/cluster-recovery/</guid><description>When a Redis Enterprise Software cluster fails, you must use the cluster configuration file and database data to recover the cluster.
Note: For cluster recovery in a Kubernetes deployment, go to: Recover a Redis Enterprise cluster on Kubernetes. Cluster failure can be caused by:
A hardware or software failure that causes the cluster to be unresponsive to client requests or administrative actions. More than half of the cluster nodes lose connection with the cluster, resulting in quorum loss.</description></item><item><title>Remove a cluster node</title><link>/rs/clusters/remove-node/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/clusters/remove-node/</guid><description>There are various reasons why you may want to remove a node in Redis Enterprise Software:
You no longer need the extra capacity, meaning you want to permanently remove the node. You would like to replace a faulty node with a healthy node. You would like to replace a healthy node with a different node. The following section explains how each of these actions can be achieved, as well as their impact and considerations.</description></item><item><title>Replace a faulty cluster node</title><link>/rs/clusters/replace-node/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/clusters/replace-node/</guid><description>If a node in your Redis Enterprise Software cluster is faulty, its status appears as Down in the Status column of the Nodes page, and in the Cluster &amp;gt; Configuration page.
To replace a faulty node:
Acquire a new node that is identical to the old node, install and configure Redis Enterprise Software on it per the install instructions.
Note: If you are using Redis on Flash, you must make sure the required flash storage is set up on this new node.</description></item></channel></rss>