<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Transport Layer Security (TLS) on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/security/tls/</link><description>Recent content in Transport Layer Security (TLS) on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/security/tls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enable TLS</title><link>/rs/security/tls/enable-tls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/tls/enable-tls/</guid><description>You can use TLS authentication for one or more of the following types of communication:
Communication from clients (applications) to your database Communication from your database to other clusters for replication using Replica Of Communication to and from your database to other clusters for synchronization using Active-Active Enable TLS for client connections You can enable TLS by editing the configuration of an existing database (as shown below) or by selecting Advanced Options when you are creating a new database.</description></item><item><title>Configure TLS protocol</title><link>/rs/security/tls/tls-protocols/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/tls/tls-protocols/</guid><description>You can change TLS protocols to improve the security of your Redis Enterprise cluster and databases. The default settings are in line with industry best practices, but you can customize them to match the security policy of your organization.
Configure TLS protocol The communications for which you can modify TLS protocols are:
Control plane - The TLS configuration for cluster administration. Data plane - The TLS configuration for the communication between applications and databases.</description></item><item><title>Configure cipher suites</title><link>/rs/security/tls/ciphers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/tls/ciphers/</guid><description>Ciphers are algorithms that help secure connections between clients and servers. You can change the ciphers to improve the security of your Redis Enterprise cluster and databases. The default settings are in line with industry best practices, but you can customize them to match the security policy of your organization.
Default cipher:
HIGH:!aNULL:!eNULL:!EXPORT:!DES:!RC4:!MD5:!PSK:!aECDH Configure cipher suites The communications for which you can modify ciphers are:
Control plane - The TLS configuration for cluster administration.</description></item></channel></rss>