<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Additional configuration on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/configuring/</link><description>Recent content in Additional configuration on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/installing-upgrading/configuring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configure AWS EC2 instances for Redis Enterprise Software</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/configuring/configuring-aws-instances/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/configuring/configuring-aws-instances/</guid><description>There are some special considerations for installing and running Redis Enterprise Software on Amazon Elastic Cloud Compute (EC2) instances.
These include:
Storage considerations Instance types Security group configuration Storage considerations AWS EC2 instances are ephemeral, but your persistent database storage should not be. If you require a persistent storage location for your database, the storage must be located outside of the instance. Therefore, when you set up an instance make sure that it has a properly sized EBS backed volume connected.</description></item><item><title>Configure CentOS/RHEL firewall</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/configuring/centos-rhel-7-firewall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/configuring/centos-rhel-7-firewall/</guid><description>CentOS/RHEL7 distributions have, by default, a restrictive firewall mechanism based on firewalld that in turn configures the standard iptables system. The default configuration assigns the network interfaces to the public zone and blocks all ports, except 22 (SSH).
Redis Enterprise Software (RS) installation on CentOS/RHEL 7 automatically creates two firewalld system services:
A service named redislabs, which includes all ports and protocols needed for communications between cluster nodes. A service named redislabs-clients, which includes the ports and protocols needed for communications external to the cluster.</description></item><item><title>Configure Swap for Linux</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/configuring/linux-swap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/configuring/linux-swap/</guid><description>Swap space is used by the Linux OS to help manage memory (pages) by copying pages from RAM to disk and the OS is configured by default to be fairly aggressive. For Redis Enterprise Software (RS) with the way it utilizes and manages memory, it is best to eliminate the likelihood of the OS swapping. If you would like to understand why, please read more on memory limits for best functionality and performance.</description></item><item><title>Change socket file locations</title><link>/rs/installing-upgrading/configuring/change-location-socket-files/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/installing-upgrading/configuring/change-location-socket-files/</guid><description>There are two default locations for the socket files in Redis Enterprise Software (RS):
/tmp - In clean installations of RS version lower than 5.2.2 /var/opt/redislabs/run - In clean installations of RS version 5.2.2 and higher We made this change because some customers have maintenance procedures that delete the /tmp directory.
When you upgrade from a RS version lower than 5.2.2 to 5.2.2 and higher, the socket files are not moved to the new location by default.</description></item></channel></rss>