<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Manage databases on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/databases/</link><description>Recent content in Manage databases on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/databases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Create a Redis Enterprise Software database</title><link>/rs/databases/create/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/databases/create/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software lets you create databases and distribute them across a cluster of nodes. These databases can use Redis Enterprise features like:
Redis on Flash High availability Data persistence Redis modules Note: For databases with Active-Active replication for geo-distributed locations, create an Active-Active database. Create a database To create a new database:
In your web browser, open the admin console of the cluster that you want to connect to in order to create the database .</description></item><item><title>Recover a failed database</title><link>/rs/databases/recover/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/databases/recover/</guid><description>When a cluster fails or a database is corrupted, you must:
Restore the cluster configuration from the CCS files Recover the databases with their previous configuration and data To restore the data that was in the databases to databases in the new cluster you must restore the database persistence files (backup, AOF, or snapshot files) to the databases. These files are stored in the persistence storage location.
The database recovery process includes:</description></item><item><title>Delete databases</title><link>/rs/databases/delete/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/databases/delete/</guid><description>When you delete a database, the database configuration and data are deleted.
Use the admin console to delete a database:
Click the relevant database row in the Databases page. The selected database page appears. Select the Configuration tab. Click Delete at the bottom of the page. Confirm the deletion.</description></item></channel></rss>