<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Manage users on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/security/access-control/manage-users/</link><description>Recent content in Manage users on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/security/access-control/manage-users/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Add users</title><link>/rs/security/access-control/manage-users/add-users/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/access-control/manage-users/add-users/</guid><description>To add a user to the cluster:
From the access control tab in the admin console, select .
Enter the name, email, and password of the new user and select a role to assign to the user.
Select internal for Authentication.
For Email Alerts, select Edit and then choose the alerts that the user should receive. You can select:
Receive alerts for databases - The alerts that are enabled for the selected databases will be sent to the user.</description></item><item><title>Manage passwords</title><link>/rs/security/access-control/manage-users/manage-passwords/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/access-control/manage-users/manage-passwords/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software provides several ways to manage the passwords of local accounts, including:
Password complexity rules
Password expiration
Password rotation policies
You can also manage a user&amp;rsquo;s ability to sign in and control session timeout.
To enforce more advanced password policies, we recommend using LDAP integration with an external identity provider, such as Active Directory.
Password complexity rules Redis Enterprise Software provides optional password complexity rules that meet common requirements.</description></item><item><title>Manage user login</title><link>/rs/security/access-control/manage-users/login-lockout/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/access-control/manage-users/login-lockout/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software secures user access in a few different ways, including automatically:
Locking user accounts after a series of authentication failures (invalid passwords)
Signing sessions out after a period of inactivity
Here, you learn how to configure the relevant settings.
User login lockout The parameters for the user login lockout are:
Login Lockout Threshold - The number of failed login attempts allowed before the user account is locked. (Default: 5 minutes) Login Lockout Counter Reset - The amount of time during which failed login attempts are counted.</description></item><item><title>Deactivate default user</title><link>/rs/security/access-control/manage-users/default-user/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/access-control/manage-users/default-user/</guid><description>When you provision a database, the default user will be enabled. This allows for backwards compatibility with versions of Redis before Redis 6.
To deactivate the default user:
Select the configuration tab. Clear the checkbox for Default database access. Select Save. Note: We recommend that you deactivate the default user when using ACLs with your database and backwards compatibility is not required.</description></item></channel></rss>