<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RedisInsight release notes on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/ri/release-notes/</link><description>Recent content in RedisInsight release notes on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/ri/release-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>RedisInsight v2.16.0, December 2022</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v.2.16.0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v.2.16.0/</guid><description>2.16.0 (December 2022) This is the General Availability (GA) release of RedisInsight 2.16.
Highlights Bulk import database connections from a file Navigation enhancements for the Tree view Pre-populated host, port, and database alias in the form when adding a new Redis database Details Features and improvements
#1492, #1497, #1500, #1502 Migrate your database connections from other Redis GUIs, including RESP.app, with the new feature to bulk import database connections from a file.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v2.14.0, November 2022</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v.2.14.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v.2.14.0/</guid><description>2.14.0 (November 2022) This is the General Availability (GA) release of RedisInsight 2.14.
Highlights Support for search capabilities in Browser: Create secondary index via dedicated form, run queries and full-text search in Browser or Tree views Ability to resize the column width of key values when displaying hashes, lists, and sorted sets Command processing time displayed as part of the result in Workbench Details Features and improvements
#1345, #1346, #1376 Added support for search capabilities in Browser tool.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v2.18.0, January 2023</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v.2.18.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v.2.18.0/</guid><description>2.18.0 (January 2023) This is the General Availability (GA) release of RedisInsight 2.18.
Highlights Support for SSH tunnel to connect to your Redis database Ability to switch between database indexes while connected to your database Recommendations on how to optimize the usage of your database Details Features and improvements
#1567, #1576, #1577 Connect to your Redis database via SSH tunnel using a password or private key in PEM format. #1540, #1608 Switch between database indexes while connected to your database in Browser, Workbench, and Database Analysis.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v2.12.0, October 2022</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v2.12.0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v2.12.0/</guid><description>2.12.0 (October 2022) This is the General Availability (GA) release of RedisInsight 2.12.
Highlights Database Analysis: Get insights and optimize the usage and performance of your Redis or Redis Stack based on the overview of the memory and data type distribution, big or complicated keys, and namespaces used Faster initial loading of the list of keys in Browser and Tree views Performance optimizations for large results in Workbench Details Features and improvements</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v2.10.0, September 2022</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v2.10.0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v2.10.0/</guid><description>2.10.0 (September 2022) This is the General Availability (GA) release of RedisInsight 2.10.
Highlights Formatters: Additional support for values of keys with Protobuf, Binary, PHP unserialize (view and edit serialized PHP values as JSON), and Java serialized objects, save formatters selected when viewing other keys New overview for cluster databases displays memory and key allocation as well as database information per shards Configure Workbench to persist the Editor after commands have been run and group the results Complete an optional user survey Details Features and improvements</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v2.8.0, August 2022</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v2.8.0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v2.8.0/</guid><description>2.8.0 (August 2022) This is the General Availability (GA) release of RedisInsight 2.8.0
Headlines Formatters: See formatted key values in JSON, MessagePack, Hex, Unicode, or ASCII in Browser/Tree view for an improved experience of working with different data formats. Clone existing database connection or connection details: Clone the database connection you previously added to have the same one, but with a different database index, username, or password. Raw mode in Workbench: Added support for the raw mode in Workbench results Details Features and improvements</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v1.13, Aug 2022</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v1.13.0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v1.13.0/</guid><description>1.13.1 (November 2022) This is the maintenance release of RedisInsight 1.13 (v1.13.1).
Fixes: Core: Fixed container vulnerabilities. Prevented healthcheck API from overloading RedisInsight DB. Earlier, a separate session was created for each healthcheck hit, which overloaded the database with too many session tokens. Now, healtcheck API doesn&amp;rsquo;t create any session tokens. Get Sentinel host using IP field. Memory Analysis: Added support for hashlistpack, zsetlistpack, quicklist2 and streamlistpack2, encoding types. 1.13.0 (August 2022) This is the General Availability Release of RedisInsight 1.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v2.6.0, July 2022</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v.2.6.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v.2.6.0/</guid><description>2.6.0 (July 2022) This is the General Availability (GA) release of RedisInsight 2.6.0
Headlines: Bulk actions: Delete the keys in bulk based on the filters set in Browser or Tree view Multiline support for key values in Browser and Tree View: Click the key value to see it in full Pipeline support in Workbench: Batch Redis commands in Workbench to optimize round-trip times In-app notifications: Receive messages about important changes, updates, or announcements inside the application.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v2.4.0, June 2022</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v.2.4.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v.2.4.0/</guid><description>2.4.0 (June 2022) This is the General Availability (GA) release of RedisInsight 2.4.0
Headlines: Pub/Sub: Added support for Redis pub/sub enabling subscription to channels and posting messages to channels. Consumer groups: Added support for streams consumer groups enabling provision of different subsets of messages from the same stream to many clients for inspection and processing. Database search: Search the list of databases added to RedisInsight to quickly find the required database.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v2.2.0, May 2022</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v2.2.0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v2.2.0/</guid><description>2.2.0 (May 2022) This is the General Availability (GA) release of RedisInsight 2.2.0
Headlines: SlowLog: New tool based on results of the Slowlog command to analyze slow operations in Redis instances Streams: Added support for Redis Streams Open the list of keys or key details in full screen Automatically refresh the list of keys and key values with a timer Details Features and improvements:
#621 , #645 , #649 Added SlowLog, a tool that displays the list of logs captured by the Slowlog command to analyze all commands that exceed a specified runtime, which helps in troubleshooting performance issues.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v1.12, May 2022</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v1.12.0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v1.12.0/</guid><description>1.12.1 (July 2022) This is the maintenance release of RedisInsight 1.12 (v1.12.1)!
Critical Bug Fix: Core: When you add or remove a Redis Enterprise Software or Redis Enterprise Cloud database in RedisInsight v1 that has the RediSearch module loaded, all hashes within that database are deleted. Fixes: Core: Added curl command to container. Fixed container vulnerabilities (CVE-2022-1292, CVE-2022-2068). RediSearch: Fixed index info to report correct information for RediSearch v2. Profiling: Added support for profiling module commands.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v2.0, Nov 2021</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v2.0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v2.0/</guid><description>2.0.6 (April 2022) This is the General Availability (GA) release of RedisInsight 2.0.6
Headlines: SNI support - added SNI support to indicate a hostname in the TLS handshake Save Profiler logs into a file - now you can save and download Profiler logs into a .TXT file Customize delimiters in Tree view - added support for custom delimiters in Tree view Support for node grouping and pulsing in RedisGraph visualizations in Workbench Details Features and improvements:</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v1.11, Oct 2021</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v1.11.0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v1.11.0/</guid><description>1.11.1 (January 2022) This is the maintenance release of RedisInsight 1.11 (v1.11.1)!
Fixes: Core: Fixed a warning about urllib version deprecation. ACL errors are now show in pretty format while in edit database screen. Fixed unnecessary warning about segment when there&amp;rsquo;s no internet connection. RediSearch: Fix index tool support for v2.2.5. Bulk actions: Added support for cross-slot bulk action execution. Fixed a bug where there&amp;rsquo;s a failure when a malformed UTF-8 characters are present in the key.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v1.10, March 2021</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v1.10.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v1.10.0/</guid><description>1.10.1 (April 2021) This is the maintenance release of RedisInsight 1.10 (v1.10.1)!
Fixes: Core: Fixed a bug where launching RedisInsight on macOS mojave (10.14.6) would log out the user. Fixed two major container vulnerability. (CVE-2021-24031, CVE-2021-24032 and CVE-2020-36242) Select existing installation path on upgrades in Windows. CLI: Added support for RAW mode (--raw in redis-cli). Browser: Fixed a bug where a number in redis string datatype is treated as a JSON .</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v1.9, January 2021</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v1.9.0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v1.9.0/</guid><description>1.9.0 (January 2021) This is the General Availability Release of RedisInsight 1.9 (v1.9.0)!
Headlines: RedisGraph tools is getting improved with better UX and new interactions capabilities Adding the ability to configure a database, by just using its direct URL to auto fill all required fields CLI is now providing ability to configure your favorite key-bindings between Emacs or Vim Full Details: Core: Support for configuration of Redis where the number of databases goes over the default 16.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v1.8, November 2020</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v1.8.0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v1.8.0/</guid><description>1.8.3 (January 2021) This is a maintenance release of RedisInsight 1.8 (v1.8.3)!
This fixes the crash on MacOS Big Sur (11.1) for the MacOS package. RedisInsight is supported on Mac hardware with Intel chips, but not for Mac hardware with the Apple M1 (ARM) chip.
1.8.2 (24 December 2020) This is the maintenance release of RedisInsight 1.8 (v1.8.2)!
Fixes: Browser: Improved handling of large strings, lists, hashes, sets and sorted sets.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v1.7, September 2020</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v1.7.0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v1.7.0/</guid><description>1.7.1 (October 2020) Maintenance release for RedisInsight 1.7 including bug fixes and enhancements.
Headlines: Core: New public health-check API to make monitoring deployments easier. Display progress information during memory analysis. Full details: Enhancements and bug fixes
Core: Fixed support for TLS in Redis Cluster databases. Application name is properly capitalized on MacOSX. Fixed update notifications on Docker - Now links to Docker Hub page and provides instructions for updating. Memory Analysis: Information about the current stage of analysis is now displayed while the analysis runs.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v1.6, June 2020</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v1.6.0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v1.6.0/</guid><description>1.6.3 (July 2020) Maintenance release for RedisInsight 1.6 including bug fixes and enhancements.
Headlines: Mac application is now getting notarized which simplifies the installation process on OS X Fixed the resize of the keys explorer allowing to see long keys Fixed filtering of keys in the browser with the filter capability in the browser Full details: Enhancements and bug fixes
Core: Mac application is properly signed and notarized on Apple services.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v1.5, May 2020</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v1.5.0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v1.5.0/</guid><description>This is the General Availability Release of RedisInsight 1.5 (v1.5.0)!
Headlines Added beta support for RedisGears module Added multi-line query editing for RediSearch, RedisGraph and Timeseries Improved support of Redis 6 ACLs Full details: Features
Core: Improved support for Redis 6 managing ACL permissions for each different capabilities Gears: Beta support for Redis Gears module Explore the latest executed functions and analyze the results or errors Manage registered functions and get execution summary Code, build and execute functions RediSearch: Multi-line for building queries RedisGraph: Multi-line for building queries Timeseries: Multi-line for building queries Bug Fixes:</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v1.4, April 2020</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v1.4.0/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v1.4.0/</guid><description>This is the General Availability Release of RedisInsight 1.4 (v1.4.0)!
Headlines Support for Redis 6, Redis Enterprise 6 and ACLs Improve CLI capabilities with removed command restrictions Full screen support in Graph, TimeSeries and RediSearch Full details: Features
Core: Added support for Redis 6 + RE6 and authentication using ACL Added Full screen support for Graph, TimeSeries and RediSearch. Improved UI consistency (colors and styles) in Graph and Timeseries CLI: Removed the command restrictions, unless a command is specifically blacklisted.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v1.3, March 2020</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v1.3.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v1.3.0/</guid><description>RedisInsight v1.3.1 release notes (April 2020) This is the maintenance release of RedisInsight 1.3 (v1.3.1).
Update urgency: Medium
Headlines Fixed support for connecting to Redis database on TLS-enabled hosts with SNI enforcement. Details Bug Fixes: Core: Fixed support for connecting to Redis database on TLS-enabled hosts with SNI enforcement. Memory Analysis Fixed wrong display of table columns in Memory Analyzer view. Browser Fixed bug where the TTL on string and RedisJSON keys was being reset on edit.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v1.2, January 2020</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v1.2.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v1.2.0/</guid><description>RedisInsight v1.2.2 release notes Update urgency: Medium
This is a maintenance release for version 1.2.
Details Bug Fixes: Core: This releases fixes the possible false positive malware issues flagged by certain antivirus vendors introduced by pyinstaller which was reported on reddit. RedisInsight v1.2.1 release notes Update urgency: Medium
This is a maintenance release for version 1.2.
Details Enhancements: Core: Upgrade notifications: When you open RedisInsight, a notification is shown if a new version is available.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v1.1, December 2019</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v1.1.0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 03:49:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v1.1.0/</guid><description>RedisInsight v1.1.0 release notes (December 2019) Headlines This release improves overall stability and provides fixes for issues found after the previous release. Details Minor Enhancements: Core: Enable mouse wheel support inside the querycard. Browser: Enable enter key press for adding keys in browser RediSearch: Disable HIGHLIGHT markup in JSON view. Browser: Improve error message when database is unreachable Add a reload/refresh button to refresh the value of a key Enable enter key press for adding keys in browser Improve error message for unsupported value types Bug Fixes: RedisGraph: Fix initial node placement in the view.</description></item><item><title>RedisInsight v1.0, November 2019</title><link>/ri/release-notes/v1.0.0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 03:49:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/release-notes/v1.0.0/</guid><description>RedisInsight v1.0.0 release notes (November 2019) This is the initial release after Redis acquired RDBTools.</description></item></channel></rss>