<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/kubernetes/reference/</link><description>Recent content in Reference on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/kubernetes/reference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Supported distributions</title><link>/kubernetes/reference/supported_k8s_distributions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/kubernetes/reference/supported_k8s_distributions/</guid><description>Each release of Redis Enterprise for Kubernetes is thoroughly tested against a set of Kubernetes distributions. The table below lists the current release&amp;rsquo;s support status for each distribution.
&amp;ldquo;supported&amp;rdquo; indicates this distribution is supported for this release. &amp;ldquo;deprecated&amp;rdquo; indicates this distribution is supported for this release, but will be dropped in a future release. Any distribution not listed below is not supported for production workloads. Kubernetes version 1.21 1.22 1.23 1.</description></item><item><title>REC custom resource options</title><link>/kubernetes/reference/cluster-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/kubernetes/reference/cluster-options/</guid><description>A Redis Enterprise cluster (REC) is defined in a custom resource definition (CRD). The REC options are specified in the spec section of the custom resource. Any field not specified in the custom resource will be set to default values by the operator. Changes made to the custom resource will override changes made to the cluster via the admin console or rladmin commands.
The most common options you might specify are listed below.</description></item><item><title>REDB custom resource options</title><link>/kubernetes/reference/db-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/kubernetes/reference/db-options/</guid><description>The database options are specified in the spec section of the database custom resource. These options include options that you can change and options that are created by the controller for applications or developers. Changes made to the REDB custom resource will override changes made to the database via the admin console or rladmin commands.
The most common options are listed below. For a complete list of options, see Redis Enterprise Database API.</description></item></channel></rss>