<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Access control on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/security/access-control/</link><description>Recent content in Access control on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/security/access-control/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configure ACLs</title><link>/rs/security/access-control/configure-acl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/access-control/configure-acl/</guid><description>Redis ACL command syntax Redis ACLs are defined by a Redis syntax where you specify the commands or command categories that are allowed for specific keys.
Note: Redis Enterprise modules do not have a command category. Redis Enterprise lets you:
Include commands and categories with the &amp;ldquo;+&amp;rdquo; prefix for commands or &amp;ldquo;+@&amp;rdquo; prefix for command categories. Exclude commands and categories with the &amp;ldquo;-&amp;rdquo; prefix for commands or &amp;ldquo;-@&amp;rdquo; prefix for command categories.</description></item><item><title>Create roles</title><link>/rs/security/access-control/create-roles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/access-control/create-roles/</guid><description>From access control &amp;gt; roles, you can configure user roles with:
Management roles - Management roles define user access to the cluster&amp;rsquo;s admin console and API. Data access controls - Data access controls define the permissions each role has for each database in the cluster. Default management roles Redis Enterprise Software includes five predefined roles that determine a user&amp;rsquo;s level of access to the admin console and REST API.
None - Cannot access the admin console or use the REST API DB Viewer - Read database settings DB Member - Administer databases Cluster Viewer - Read cluster settings Cluster Member - Administer the cluster Admin - Full cluster access For more details about the privileges granted by each of these roles, see admin console permissions or REST API permissions.</description></item><item><title>Access control for Active-Active databases</title><link>/rs/security/access-control/active-active/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/access-control/active-active/</guid><description>Users, roles, and Redis ACLs Users, roles, and Redis ACLs are cluster-level entities. Therefore they are applied per local participating cluster and Active-Active database instance, and they are not replicated or propagated to the other participating clusters and instances. ACLs will be enforced according to the instance the client is connected to. The Active-Active replication mechanism will propagate all the effects of the operation.
Update admin credentials Active-Active databases use administrator credentials to manage operations.</description></item></channel></rss>