<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Administration on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/</link><description>Recent content in Administration on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/ri/using-redisinsight/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Add a Redis database</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/add-instance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 03:49:29 +0530</pubDate><guid>/ri/using-redisinsight/add-instance/</guid><description>Before using any of the tools to work with your database, you must first add the database so RedisInsight can connect to it.
Each of these database configurations requires specific steps to add them to RedisInsight:
Standalone Redis Redis cluster Redis Sentinel Redis with TLS authentication Elasticache Note: Currently, RedisInsight supports Redis versions 4 and newer. Add a standalone Redis database This is the simplest setup of a Redis database with just a single Redis server.</description></item><item><title>Automatically Discovering Databases</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/auto-discover-databases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/using-redisinsight/auto-discover-databases/</guid><description>RedisInsight lets you automatically add Redis Enterprise Software and Redis Enterprise Cloud databases.
Note: For Redis Cloud, auto-discovery is supported only for Flexible or Annual subscriptions. Auto-discovery for Redis Software To automatically discover and add Redit Software databases to RedisInsight:
In RedisInsight, select ADD REDIS DATABASE.
Select Automatically Discover Databases.
Select Redis Enterprise.
Enter the connection details and then select DISCOVER DATABASES.
From the list of databases, choose the databases that you want to add and then select ADD SELECTED DATABASES.</description></item><item><title>Adding Databases Programmatically</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/api/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/using-redisinsight/api/</guid><description>If you have a lot of Redis databases or you are using RedisInsight as part of some automated workflow, you might want to add databases programmatically.
Now this is possible using our experimental REST API. Below is the documentation for the endpoints required to add databases.
Note that this API should not be considered stable at this point and might change or break entirely in future releases. Do not rely on this API for production.</description></item><item><title>Adding Databases via GET URL</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/api-get/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/using-redisinsight/api-get/</guid><description>If you want to automate adding a Redis database without filling the database form, you might want to add database via GET URL.
Below is the documentation for the URL required to add databases.
Add Redis database Used to add Redis databases to RedisInsight.
URL : /add/
Method : GET
Query Parameters These are the required query parameters for any type of database.
Parameter Type Required/Optional Description host string required Hostname of your Redis database.</description></item><item><title>Authenticate database users</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/auth-database/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/using-redisinsight/auth-database/</guid><description>You can enforce authentication of users who share your databases by running Redisinsight with variables RIAUTHPROMPT, RIAUTHTIMER, and RILOGLEVEL. For more information on variables, see Configure RedisInsight.
By setting the variables, enforce the prompt for username and password each time the database is opened and at a specific time interval while users work with the database. You can maintain multiple tabs with the same database without having to enter username and password in each one.</description></item><item><title>Proxy</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/proxy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 03:49:29 +0530</pubDate><guid>/ri/using-redisinsight/proxy/</guid><description>Trusted origins By default, RedisInsight trusts only the origin to which RedisInsight binds to. If RedisInsight is run behind a proxy, the origin where the requests come from is not trusted if the proxy&amp;rsquo;s origin is not the origin where RedisInsight binds to. While RedisInsight does start and is reachable, no operations are allowed. Because the origin of requests/proxy is always known, the trusted origins must be manually set via the RITRUSTEDORIGINS environment variable.</description></item><item><title>Performance Metrics</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/overview/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 03:49:29 +0530</pubDate><guid>/ri/using-redisinsight/overview/</guid><description>RedisInsight Overview provides you the quick overview about your Redis instance through graphical representation. It displays the total memory and keys for your instance. Number of connections received, clients connected, Network input and output and various other information.</description></item><item><title>Cluster Management</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/cluster-management/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 03:49:29 +0530</pubDate><guid>/ri/using-redisinsight/cluster-management/</guid><description>RedisInsight Cluster Management provides a graphical user interface (GUI) to manage your Redis Cluster. Cluster Management comes with three different views to analyze your cluster architecture.
Master Layout - This view only contains information about the masters present in the Redis Cluster. The information present is - slot ranges, host, port and few metrics gathered from redis INFO Command. Master-Replica Layout - This view contains masters along with their replicas. This view contains information about slots ranges, host, port, etc for both master and replica.</description></item><item><title>Browser</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/browser/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 12:33:02 +0530</pubDate><guid>/ri/using-redisinsight/browser/</guid><description>RedisInsight Browser lets you explore keys in your redis server. You can add, edit and delete a key. You can even update the key expiry and copy the key name to be used in different places of the application.
Note: RedisInsight restricts visualization of keys that are greater than 2GB in size.</description></item><item><title>CLI</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/cli/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 03:49:29 +0530</pubDate><guid>/ri/using-redisinsight/cli/</guid><description>RedisInsight CLI lets you run commands against a redis server. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to remember the syntax - the integrated help shows you all the arguments and validates your command as you type.
Key Bindings Emacs and Vim keybindings are supported.
Action Emacs Vim Previous history item C-p k Next history item C-n j Move cursor to the begining C-a 0 Move cursor to the end C-e $ Move cursor to the right by one character C-f h Move cursor to the left by one character C-b l Enter insert mode - i Enter normal mode - ESC</description></item><item><title>Memory analysis</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/memory-analysis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 03:49:29 +0530</pubDate><guid>/ri/using-redisinsight/memory-analysis/</guid><description>RedisInsight Memory analysis helps you analyze your Redis database, which can reduce memory use and improve application performance.
Analysis can be done in two ways:
online mode - In this mode, RedisInsight downloads an rdb file from your connected Redis instance and analyzes it to create a temp file with all the keys and metadata required for analysis. In case there is a master-replica connection, RedisInsight downloads the dump from the replica instead of the master in order to avoid affecting the performance of the master.</description></item><item><title>Profiler</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/profiler/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 03:49:29 +0530</pubDate><guid>/ri/using-redisinsight/profiler/</guid><description>RedisInsight Profiler runs Redis MONITOR command, which analyzes every command sent to the redis instance. It parses the output of the MONITOR command and generates a summarized view. All the commands sent to the redis instance are monitored for the duration of the profiling.
Profiler gives information about the number of commands processed, commands/second and number of connected clients. It also gives information about top prefixes, top keys and top commands.</description></item><item><title>Slowlog</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/slowlog/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 03:49:29 +0530</pubDate><guid>/ri/using-redisinsight/slowlog/</guid><description>RedisInsight Slowlog is a list of slow operations for your redis instance. These can be used to troubleshoot performance issues. Each entry in the list displays the command, duration and timestamp. Any transaction that exceeds slowlog-log-slower-than microseconds are recorded up to a maximum of slowlog-max-len after which older entries are discarded.
Clear Slowlog - Clear slowlog clears all the slowlog entries from your redis server.</description></item><item><title>Configuration</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/configuration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 03:49:29 +0530</pubDate><guid>/ri/using-redisinsight/configuration/</guid><description>RedisInsight configuration allows to update your redis instance&amp;rsquo;s config with its easy to use config editor. Each of the keys shown corresponds to an entry in the Redis configuration file. Most of the configuration settings can be applied without restarting the server. Also, it comes with an option of rewriting your current settings to your redis.conf file so that these settings remain even when server restarts.
Configurations are also separated into categories like- Advanced config, Security, Lua Scripting etc.</description></item><item><title>View Java Serialized Objects in Redis</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/java-serialized-objects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/using-redisinsight/java-serialized-objects/</guid><description>RedisInsight detects java serialized objects and converts them to a nicely formatted JSON object, along with the fully qualified class name.
It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter what you store. Whether it is a hibernate object, or a user session or a plain old java object, RedisInsight reverse-engineers and show it to you nicely.
Just for fun, we tried out how such an object would look without the formatting.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting RedisInsight</title><link>/ri/using-redisinsight/troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 10:49:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ri/using-redisinsight/troubleshooting/</guid><description>When RedisInsight doesn&amp;rsquo;t behave as expected, use these steps to see what the problem is.
For additional configuration options, such as changing the default port, go to: https://docs.redislabs.com/latest/ri/installing/configurations/
Logs To get detailed information about errors in RedisInsight, you can review the log files with the .log extension in:
Docker: In the /db/ directory inside the container. Mac: In the /Users/&amp;lt;your-username&amp;gt;/.redisinsight directory. Windows: In the C:\Users\&amp;lt;your-username&amp;gt;\.redisinsight directory. Linux: In the /home/&amp;lt;your-username&amp;gt;/.redisinsight directory.</description></item></channel></rss>