<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Install and upgrade modules on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/modules/install/</link><description>Recent content in Install and upgrade modules on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/modules/install/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Install a module on a cluster</title><link>/modules/install/add-module-to-cluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/install/add-module-to-cluster/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise comes packaged with several modules. You can view the installed modules and their versions from settings &amp;gt; redis modules in the Redis Enterprise admin console.
To use other modules or upgrade an existing module to a more recent version, you need to install the new module package on your cluster.
Note: Modules are not supported in Redis Enterprise Software on RHEL/CentOS 6.x. Get packaged modules To install or upgrade a module on a Redis Enterprise cluster, you need a module package.</description></item><item><title>Enable a module for a database</title><link>/modules/install/add-module-to-database/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/install/add-module-to-database/</guid><description>Modules add additional functionality to Redis databases for specific use cases. You can enable modules when you create a database.
Prerequisites Installed the module on the cluster Upgraded the module to the latest version Create a database with a module Note: You can only add modules to a database when you first create it. You cannot add modules to an existing database. In the Redis Enterprise admin console, follow these steps to add modules to a database:</description></item><item><title>Upgrade modules</title><link>/modules/install/upgrade-module/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/install/upgrade-module/</guid><description>Upgrade a module in Redis Enterprise to get the latest features and fixes.
Note: If you upgrade a single-node cluster, it does not load the new modules that are bundled with the new cluster version.
Before you upgrade a database with the RediSearch module enabled to Redis 5.0, you must upgrade the RediSearch module to version 1.4.2 or later.
Prerequisites Before you upgrade a module enabled in a database, install the new version of the module on the cluster.</description></item><item><title>Package modules</title><link>/modules/install/packaging-modules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/install/packaging-modules/</guid><description>In addition to the modules packaged and certified by Redis, there are many custom modules that are compatible with Redis Enterprise.
To use custom modules with a Redis Enterprise database, you need to package them with the RAMP (Redis Automatic Module Packaging) utility before you install them on the cluster.
Warning - Redis does not officially support third-party modules or databases created with them. Prerequisites Install the ramp-packer utility:
pip install ramp-packer Package custom modules Before you can install and enable a custom module in a new database, you need to download, compile, and package it with the RAMP utility.</description></item></channel></rss>