<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RedisGears readers on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/modules/redisgears/jvm/classes/readers/</link><description>Recent content in RedisGears readers on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/modules/redisgears/jvm/classes/readers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CommandOverrider</title><link>/modules/redisgears/jvm/classes/readers/commandoverrider/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/redisgears/jvm/classes/readers/commandoverrider/</guid><description>The CommandOverrider allows you to override and customize Redis commands.
Pass the CommandOverrider to the GearsBuilder.CreateGearsBuilder() function in your Java code. Call the register() function. Run RG.JEXECUTE to register your code. Note: If you register code that uses CommandOverrider, its reader value is &amp;quot;CommandReader&amp;quot; when you run the RG.DUMPREGISTRATIONS command, not &amp;quot;CommandOverrider&amp;quot;. Parameters Name Type Description command string The command to override prefix string Only override the command for keys that start with this string Output records Outputs a record with the command&amp;rsquo;s name and arguments.</description></item><item><title>CommandReader</title><link>/modules/redisgears/jvm/classes/readers/commandreader/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/redisgears/jvm/classes/readers/commandreader/</guid><description>The CommandReader allows you to run RedisGears functions on command when you:
Pass the CommandReader to the GearsBuilder.CreateGearsBuilder() function in your Java code.
Call the register() function.
Run RG.JEXECUTE to register your code.
Use RG.TRIGGER to run your code on command:
RG.TRIGGER &amp;lt;Trigger name&amp;gt; [arg1 arg2 ...] Parameters Name Type Description trigger string The command name that triggers the registered RedisGears functions to run Output records Outputs a record with the command trigger&amp;rsquo;s name and arguments.</description></item><item><title>JavaReader</title><link>/modules/redisgears/jvm/classes/readers/javareader/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/redisgears/jvm/classes/readers/javareader/</guid><description>The JavaReader is an abstract class that allows you to create a custom reader in Java.
Create a custom reader To create a custom reader:
Extend the JavaReader class Override the iterator() function Custom reader example The implementation of the KeysOnlyReader class shows how to create a custom reader with JavaReader:
import java.util.Iterator; import gears.GearsBuilder; /** * A reader that only reads key names from the key space * */ public class KeysOnlyReader extends JavaReader&amp;lt;String&amp;gt; { /** * */ private static final long serialVersionUID = 1L; private String scanSize; private String pattern; /** * Create a new KeysOnlyReader reader * @param scanSize - the size to use with the scan command * @param pattern - the pattern of the keys to read */ public KeysOnlyReader(int scanSize, String pattern) { this.</description></item><item><title>KeysOnlyReader</title><link>/modules/redisgears/jvm/classes/readers/keysonlyreader/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/redisgears/jvm/classes/readers/keysonlyreader/</guid><description>The KeysOnlyReader only extracts the key names from a database.
Constructors You can use one of these constructors to create a new KeysOnlyReader object:
public KeysOnlyReader() public KeysOnlyReader(int scanSize, String pattern) Parameters Name Type Default value Description pattern string &amp;ldquo;*&amp;rdquo; (match all keys) Get all keys that match this pattern scanSize integer 10000 The scan command&amp;rsquo;s size limit Output records Each output record is a string that represents the key&amp;rsquo;s name.</description></item><item><title>KeysReader</title><link>/modules/redisgears/jvm/classes/readers/keysreader/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/redisgears/jvm/classes/readers/keysreader/</guid><description>Creates records from the keys and values stored in a Redis database.
Note: Currently only supports string and hash data types. For other data types, it will only extract the key name. Constructors You can use one of these constructors to create a new KeysReader object:
public KeysReader() public KeysReader(String pattern) public KeysReader(String prefix, boolean readValues) public KeysReader(String pattern, boolean noScan, boolean readValues) public KeysReader(String prefix, boolean readValues, String[] eventTypes, String[] keyTypes) public KeysReader(String pattern, boolean noScan, boolean readValues, String[] eventTypes, String[] keyTypes) Parameters Name Type Default value Description commands array of strings null The commands that this reader is registered on eventTypes array of strings null The event types to register on (usually the command name) keyTypes array of strings null The key types to register on noScan boolean false Whether or not to scan the key space or just read the pattern as is pattern/prefix string &amp;ldquo;*&amp;rdquo; (match all keys) The reader will get all keys that match this pattern readValues boolean true Whether or not to read the keys&amp;rsquo; values Output records Creates a KeysReaderRecord for each matching key in the database.</description></item><item><title>ShardsIDReader</title><link>/modules/redisgears/jvm/classes/readers/shardsidreader/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/redisgears/jvm/classes/readers/shardsidreader/</guid><description>The ShardsIDReader creates a single record on each shard that represents the current shard&amp;rsquo;s ID.
Use this reader when you want to run an operation on each shard in the database.
Parameters None
Output records Creates a record for each shard with the shard&amp;rsquo;s cluster identifier.
Example ShardsIDReader reader = new ShardsIDReader();</description></item><item><title>StreamReader</title><link>/modules/redisgears/jvm/classes/readers/streamreader/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/modules/redisgears/jvm/classes/readers/streamreader/</guid><description>Reads Redis stream data.
Parameters Name Type Default value Description batchSize integer 1 The number of new messages that will cause the functions to run duration integer 0 How many seconds to wait before execution, regardless of batch size failurePolicy FailurePolicy FailurePolicy.CONTINUE How to handle execution failure (CONTINUE/ABORT/RETRY) failureRetryInterval integer 5000 The number of seconds to wait before retrying pattern string &amp;ldquo;*&amp;rdquo; (match all keys) The pattern of keys that store streams startId string &amp;ldquo;0-0&amp;rdquo; Start reading from this stream ID trimStream boolean true Whether or not to trim the stream Output records Creates a record for each message in the input stream.</description></item></channel></rss>