<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>REST API on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/</link><description>Recent content in REST API on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/references/rest-api/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Redis Enterprise Software REST API quick start</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/quick-start/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software includes a REST API that allows you to automate certain tasks. This article shows you how to send a request to the Redis Enterprise Software REST API.
Fundamentals No matter which method you use to send API requests, there are a few common concepts to remember.
Type Description Authentication Use Basic Auth with your cluster username (email) and password Ports All calls are made to port 9443 by default Versions Specify the version in the request URI Headers Accept and Content-Type should be application/json Response types and error codes A response of 200 OK means success; otherwise, the request failed due to an error For more information, see Redis Enterprise Software REST API.</description></item><item><title>Permissions</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/permissions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/permissions/</guid><description>Some Redis Enterprise REST API requests may require the user to have specific permissions.
Administrators can assign a predefined role to a user via the admin console or a PUT /users/{uid} API request in order to grant necessary permissions to them.
Roles Each user in the cluster has an assigned role, which defines the permissions granted to the user.
Available roles include:
db_viewer: Can view database info. db_member: Can create or modify databases and view their info.</description></item></channel></rss>