<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Statistics on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/statistics/</link><description>Recent content in Statistics on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/references/rest-api/objects/statistics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cluster metrics</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/statistics/cluster-metrics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/statistics/cluster-metrics/</guid><description>Metric name Type Description available_flash float Sum of available flash in all nodes (bytes) available_memory float Sum of available memory in all nodes (bytes) avg_latency float Average latency of requests handled by all cluster endpoints (micro-sec); returned only when there is traffic bigstore_free float Sum of free space of backend flash (used by flash DB&amp;rsquo;s BigRedis) on all cluster nodes (bytes); only returned when BigRedis is enabled bigstore_iops float Rate of I/O operations against backend flash for all shards which are part of a flash-based DB (BigRedis) in the cluster (ops/sec); returned only when BigRedis is enabled bigstore_kv_ops float Rate of value read/write operations against back-end flash for all shards which are part of a flash based DB (BigRedis) in cluster (ops/sec); only returned when BigRedis is enabled bigstore_throughput float Throughput I/O operations against backend flash for all shards which are part of a flash-based DB (BigRedis) in the cluster (bytes/sec); only returned when BigRedis is enabled conns float Total number of clients connected to all cluster endpoints cpu_idle float CPU idle time portion, the value is weighted between all nodes based on number of cores in each node (0-1, multiply by 100 to get percent) cpu_system float CPU time portion spent in kernel on the cluster, the value is weighted between all nodes based on number of cores in each node (0-1, multiply by 100 to get percent) cpu_user float CPU time portion spent by users-pace processes on the cluster.</description></item><item><title>DB metrics</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/statistics/db-metrics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/statistics/db-metrics/</guid><description>Metric name Type Description avg_latency float Average latency of operations on the DB (microseconds). Only returned when there is traffic. avg_other_latency float Average latency of other (non read/write) operations (microseconds). Only returned when there is traffic. avg_read_latency float Average latency of read operations (microseconds). Only returned when there is traffic. avg_write_latency float Average latency of write operations (microseconds). Only returned when there is traffic. big_del_flash float Rate of key deletes for keys on flash (BigRedis) (key access/sec).</description></item><item><title>Node metrics</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/statistics/node-metrics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/statistics/node-metrics/</guid><description> Metric name Type Description available_flash float Available flash on the node (bytes) available_memory float Available RAM on the node (bytes) avg_latency float Average latency of requests handled by endpoints on the node (micro-sec); returned only when there is traffic bigstore_free float Free space of backend flash (used by flash DB&amp;rsquo;s BigRedis) (bytes); returned only when BigRedis is enabled bigstore_iops float Rate of I/O operations against backend flash for all shards which are part of a flash-based DB (BigRedis) on the node (ops/sec); returned only when BigRedis is enabled bigstore_kv_ops float Rate of value read/write operations against backend flash for all shards which are part of a flash-based DB (BigRedis) on the node (ops/sec); returned only when BigRedis is enabled bigstore_throughput float Throughput of I/O operations against backend flash for all shards which are part of a flash-based DB (BigRedis) on the node (bytes/sec); returned only when BigRedis is enabled conns float Number of clients connected to endpoints on the node cpu_idle float CPU idle time portion (0-1, multiply by 100 to get percent) cpu_system float CPU time portion spent in kernel (0-1, multiply by 100 to get percent) cpu_user float CPU time portion spent by users-pace processes (0-1, multiply by 100 to get percent) cur_aof_rewrites float Number of current AOF rewrites by shards on this node egress_bytes float Rate of outgoing network traffic to the node (bytes/sec) ephemeral_storage_avail float Disk space available to Redis Enterprise processes on configured ephemeral disk (bytes) ephemeral_storage_free float Free disk space on configured ephemeral disk (bytes) free_memory float Free memory on the node (bytes) ingress_bytes float Rate of incoming network traffic to the node (bytes/sec) persistent_storage_avail float Disk space available to Redis Enterprise processes on configured persistent disk (bytes) persistent_storage_free float Free disk space on configured persistent disk (bytes) provisional_flash float Amount of flash available for new shards on this node, taking into account overbooking, max Redis servers, reserved flash, and provision and migration thresholds (bytes) provisional_memory float Amount of RAM available for new shards on this node, taking into account overbooking, max Redis servers, reserved memory, and provision and migration thresholds (bytes) total_req float Request rate handled by endpoints on the node (ops/sec)</description></item><item><title>Shard metrics</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/statistics/shard-metrics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/statistics/shard-metrics/</guid><description>Metric name Type Description aof_rewrite_inprog float The number of simultaneous AOF rewrites that are in progress avg_ttl float Estimated average time to live of a random key (msec) big_del_flash float Rate of key deletes for keys on flash (BigRedis) (key access/sec). Only returned when BigRedis is enabled. big_del_ram float Rate of key deletes for keys in RAM (BigRedis) (key access/sec); this includes write misses (new keys created). Only returned when BigRedis is enabled.</description></item></channel></rss>