<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Configure clusters on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/clusters/configure/</link><description>Recent content in Configure clusters on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/clusters/configure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cluster settings</title><link>/rs/clusters/configure/cluster-settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/clusters/configure/cluster-settings/</guid><description>You can view and set various cluster settings such as cluster name, email service, time zone, and license in the Settings &amp;gt; General page.
Entering a cluster key After purchasing a cluster key and if your account has the &amp;ldquo;Admin&amp;rdquo; role, you can enter the key in the Cluster Key field, either during initial
cluster creation or at any time afterward. The key defines various cluster settings, such as the maximum number of shards you can have in the cluster.</description></item><item><title>Cluster license keys</title><link>/rs/clusters/configure/license-keys/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/clusters/configure/license-keys/</guid><description>The cluster key (or license) enables features and capacity within Redis Enterprise Software (RS). You can add or update a cluster key at any time in a cluster lifecycle. When the cluster does not have a cluster key, the cluster is in trial mode.
Trial mode Trial mode is limited to thirty days and a total of four shards, including master and replica shards. Any new installation starts its thirty-day clock from the day the cluster setup was done (with the first cluster node provisioned).</description></item><item><title>Synchronize cluster node clocks</title><link>/rs/clusters/configure/sync-clocks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/clusters/configure/sync-clocks/</guid><description>To avoid problems with internal cluster communications that can impact your data integrity, make sure that the clocks on all of the cluster nodes are synchronized using Chrony and/or NTP.
When you install Redis Enterprise Software, the install script checks if Chrony or NTP is running. If they are not, the installation process asks for permission to configure a scheduled Cron job. This should make sure that the node&amp;rsquo;s clock is always synchronized.</description></item><item><title>Rack-zone awareness in Redis Enterprise Software</title><link>/rs/clusters/configure/rack-zone-awareness/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/clusters/configure/rack-zone-awareness/</guid><description>Rack-zone awareness is a Redis Enterprise feature that helps to ensure high-availability in the event of a rack or zone failure.
When you enable rack-zone awareness in a Redis Enterprise Software cluster, you assign a rack-zone ID to each node. This ID is used to map the node to a physical rack or logical zone. The cluster can then ensure that master shards, corresponding replica shards, and associated endpoints are placed on nodes in different racks/zones.</description></item></channel></rss>