<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LDAP authentication on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/security/access-control/ldap/</link><description>Recent content in LDAP authentication on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/security/access-control/ldap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enable role-based LDAP</title><link>/rs/security/access-control/ldap/enable-role-based-ldap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/access-control/ldap/enable-role-based-ldap/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software uses a role-based mechanism to enable LDAP authentication and authorization.
When a user attempts to access Redis Enterprise resources using LDAP credentials, the credentials are passed to the LDAP server in a bind request. If the request succeeds, the user’s groups are searched for a group that authorizes access to the original resource.
Role-based LDAP lets you authorize admin console admins (previously known as external users) as well as database users.</description></item><item><title>Map LDAP groups to roles</title><link>/rs/security/access-control/ldap/map-ldap-groups-to-roles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/access-control/ldap/map-ldap-groups-to-roles/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software uses a role-based mechanism to enable LDAP authentication and authorization.
Once LDAP is enabled, you need to map LDAP groups to Redis Enterprise access control roles.
Map LDAP groups to roles To map LDAP groups to access control roles:
From the admin console menu, select Access control &amp;gt; LDAP mappings.
If you see an &amp;ldquo;LDAP configuration is disabled&amp;rdquo; message, go to Settings &amp;gt; LDAP to enable role-based LDAP.</description></item><item><title>Update database ACLs</title><link>/rs/security/access-control/ldap/update-database-acls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/access-control/ldap/update-database-acls/</guid><description>To grant LDAP users access to a database, assign the mapped access role to the access control list (ACL) for the database.
From the admin console menu, select Databases and then select the database from the list.
Select the Configuration tab to display the database details.
Select the Edit button.
Locate the Access Control List setting and select its Add button.
Select the appropriate roles and then save your changes.</description></item><item><title>Migrate to role-based LDAP</title><link>/rs/security/access-control/ldap/migrate-to-role-based-ldap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/access-control/ldap/migrate-to-role-based-ldap/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Software supports LDAP through a role-based mechanism, first introduced in v6.0.20.
Earlier versions of Redis Enterprise Software supported a cluster-based mechanism; however, that mechanism was removed in v6.2.12.
If you&amp;rsquo;re using the cluster-based mechanism to enable LDAP authentication, you need to migrate to the role-based mechanism before upgrading to Redis Enterprise Software v6.2.12 or later.
Migration checklist This checklist covers the basic process:
Identify accounts per app on the customer end.</description></item><item><title>Cluster-based LDAP authentication</title><link>/rs/security/access-control/ldap/cluster-based-ldap-authentication/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/access-control/ldap/cluster-based-ldap-authentication/</guid><description>&lt;div class="panel panel-primary panel-warning">&lt;i class="icon-Warning">&lt;/i>
&lt;div class="panel-content">&lt;span class="panel-heading">Warning - &lt;/span>
&lt;div class="panel-body">&lt;p>As of v6.2.12, the features described in this article are &lt;a href="../../../../glossary/#obsolete">obsolete&lt;/a> and have been removed from Redis Enterprise Software.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="../../../../rs/release-notes/rs-6-0-20-april-2021/">Version 6.0.20&lt;/a> introduced a &lt;a href="../../../../rs/security/access-control/ldap/">role-based LDAP integration&lt;/a> that replaced the cluster-based integration described here.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At the time, the earlier integration remained in order to provide a transition period for migration. That period has now passed and the cluster-based integration has been removed.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This article has been archived and will no longer be maintained.&lt;/p>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;p>Redis Enterprise Software supports Lightweight Directory Access Protocol (LDAP).&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>