<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloud database security on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rc/security/database-security/</link><description>Recent content in Cloud database security on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rc/security/database-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Passwords, users, and roles</title><link>/rc/security/database-security/passwords-users-roles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/security/database-security/passwords-users-roles/</guid><description>All Redis Cloud databases require either password-based authentication or role-based access control. Role-based access control lets you define multiple users with fine-grained authorization features.
Prerequisites To use role-based access control, your Redis Cloud database needs to support Redis version 6.0.0 or later.
The Redis version of a database is displayed in the General section of the Configuration tab of the database detail screen.
Password-based authentication Password-based authentication is a basic but essential Redis security feature.</description></item><item><title>Transport Layer Security (TLS)</title><link>/rc/security/database-security/tls-ssl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/security/database-security/tls-ssl/</guid><description>Transport Layer Security (TLS) uses encryption to secure network communications.
Redis Cloud Fixed, Flexible, and Annual subscriptions can use TLS to encrypt data communications between applications and Redis databases.
Use TLS with Redis Cloud TLS is not enabled by default.
TLS recommendations Because TLS has an impact on performance, you need to determine whether the security benefits of TLS are worth the performance impact. TLS recommendations depend on the subscription plan and whether clients connect to your database using public or private endpoints.</description></item><item><title>Network security</title><link>/rc/security/database-security/network-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rc/security/database-security/network-security/</guid><description>Redis Enterprise Cloud supports two types of network security: database-level CIDR allow lists and VPC-wide CIDR allow lists.
These features are available in most Redis Cloud configurations, as shown here:
Cloud provider VPC peering IP restrictions AWS Flexible and Annual Fixed (paid), Flexible, and Annual GCP Flexible and Annual Fixed (paid), Flexible, and Annual Azure Annual Annual IP and subnet restrictions You can restrict database access to a configurable set of source IP addresses and subnets.</description></item></channel></rss>