<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Security on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/security/</link><description>Recent content in Security on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Audit connection events</title><link>/rs/security/audit-events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/audit-events/</guid><description>Starting with version 6.2.18, Redis Enterprise Software lets you audit database connection and authentication events. This helps you track and troubleshoot connection activity.
The following events are tracked:
Database connection attempts Authentication requests, including requests for new and existing connections Database disconnects When tracked events are triggered, notifications are sent via TCP to an address and port defined when auditing is enabled. Notifications appear in near real time and are intended to be consumed by an external listener, such as a TCP listener, third-party service, or related utility.</description></item><item><title>Internode encryption</title><link>/rs/security/internode-encryption/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/security/internode-encryption/</guid><description>As of v6.2.4, Redis Enterprise Software supports internode encryption, which encrypts internal communication between nodes. This improves the security of data as it travels within a cluster.
Internode encryption is enabled for the control plane, which manages the cluster and its databases.
Internode encryption is supported for the data plane, which encrypts communication used to replicate shards between nodes and proxy communication with shards located on different nodes.
The following diagram shows how this works.</description></item></channel></rss>