<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rladmin on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/</link><description>Recent content in rladmin on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>rladmin bind</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/bind/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/bind/</guid><description>Manages the proxy policy for a specific database endpoint.
bind endpoint exclude Defines a list of nodes to exclude from the proxy policy for a specific database endpoint. When you exclude a node, the endpoint cannot bind to the node&amp;rsquo;s proxy.
Each time you run an exclude command, it overwrites the previous list of excluded nodes.
rladmin bind [ db { db:&amp;lt;id&amp;gt; | &amp;lt;name&amp;gt; } ] endpoint &amp;lt;id&amp;gt; exclude &amp;lt;proxy_id1 .</description></item><item><title>rladmin failover</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/failover/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/failover/</guid><description>Fails over one or more primary (also known as master) shards of a database and promotes their respective replicas to primary shards.
rladmin failover [db { db:&amp;lt;id&amp;gt; | &amp;lt;name&amp;gt; }] shard &amp;lt;id1 ... idN&amp;gt; [immediate] Parameters Parameter Type/Value Description db db:&amp;lt;id&amp;gt;
name Fail over shards for the specified database shard one or more primary shard IDs Primary shard or shards to fail over immediate Perform failover without verifying the replica shards are in full sync with the master shards Returns Returns Finished successfully if the failover completed.</description></item><item><title>rladmin help</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/help/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/help/</guid><description>Lists all options and parameters for rladmin commands.
rladmin help [command] Parameters Parameter Description command Display help for this rladmin command (optional) Returns Returns a list of available rladmin commands.
If a command is specified, returns a list of all the options and parameters for that rladmin command.
Example $ rladmin help usage: rladmin [options] [command] [command args] Options: -y Assume Yes for all required user confirmations. Commands: bind Bind an endpoint cluster Cluster management commands exit Exit admin shell failover Fail-over master to slave help Show available commands, or use help &amp;lt;command&amp;gt; for a specific command info Show information about tunable parameters migrate Migrate elements between nodes node Node management commands placement Configure shards placement policy recover Recover databases restart Restart database shards status Show status information suffix Suffix management tune Tune system parameters upgrade Upgrade entity version verify Cluster verification reports Use &amp;#34;rladmin help [command]&amp;#34; to get more information on a specific command.</description></item><item><title>rladmin info</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/info/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/info/</guid><description>Shows the current configuration of specified databases, proxies, clusters, or nodes.
info cluster Lists the current configuration for the cluster.
rladmin info cluster Parameters None
Returns Returns the current configuration for the cluster.
Example $ rladmin info cluster Cluster configuration: repl_diskless: enabled shards_overbooking: disabled default_non_sharded_proxy_policy: single default_sharded_proxy_policy: single default_shards_placement: dense default_fork_evict_ram: enabled default_provisioned_redis_version: 6.0 redis_migrate_node_threshold: 0KB (0 bytes) redis_migrate_node_threshold_percent: 4 (%) redis_provision_node_threshold: 0KB (0 bytes) redis_provision_node_threshold_percent: 12 (%) max_simultaneous_backups: 4 slave_ha: enabled slave_ha_grace_period: 600 slave_ha_cooldown_period: 3600 slave_ha_bdb_cooldown_period: 7200 parallel_shards_upgrade: 0 show_internals: disabled expose_hostnames_for_all_suffixes: disabled login_lockout_threshold: 5 login_lockout_duration: 1800 login_lockout_counter_reset_after: 900 default_concurrent_restore_actions: 10 endpoint_rebind_propagation_grace_time: 15 data_internode_encryption: disabled redis_upgrade_policy: major db_conns_auditing: disabled watchdog profile: local-network http support: enabled upgrade mode: disabled cm_session_timeout_minutes: 15 cm_port: 8443 cnm_http_port: 8080 cnm_https_port: 9443 info db Shows the current configuration for databases.</description></item><item><title>rladmin migrate</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/migrate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/migrate/</guid><description>Moves Redis Enterprise shards or endpoints to a new node in the same cluster.
migrate all_master_shards Moves all primary shards of a specified database or node to a new node in the same cluster.
rladmin migrate { db { db:&amp;lt;id&amp;gt; | &amp;lt;name&amp;gt; } | node &amp;lt;origin node ID&amp;gt; } all_master_shards target_node &amp;lt;id&amp;gt; [ override_policy ] Parameters Parameter Type/Value Description db db:&amp;lt;id&amp;gt;
name Limits migration to a specific database node integer Limits migration to a specific origin node target_node integer Migration target node override_policy Overrides the rack aware policy and allows primary and replica shards on the same node Returns Returns Done if the migration completed successfully.</description></item><item><title>rladmin placement</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/placement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/placement/</guid><description>Configures the shard placement policy for a specified database.
rladmin placement db { db:&amp;lt;id&amp;gt; | &amp;lt;name&amp;gt; } { dense | sparse } Parameters Parameter Type/Value Description db db:&amp;lt;id&amp;gt;
name Configures shard placement for the specified database dense Places new shards on the same node as long as it has resources sparse Places new shards on the maximum number of available nodes within the cluster Returns Returns the new shard placement policy if the policy was changed successfully.</description></item><item><title>rladmin recover</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/recover/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/recover/</guid><description>Recovers databases in recovery mode.
recover all Recovers all databases in recovery mode.
rladmin recover all [ only_configuration ] Parameters Parameters Type/Value Description only_configuration Recover database configuration without data Returns Returns Completed successfully if the database was recovered. Otherwise, returns an error.
recover db Recovers a specific database in recovery mode.
rladmin recover db { db:&amp;lt;id&amp;gt; | &amp;lt;name&amp;gt; } [ only_configuration ] Parameters Parameters Type/Value Description db db:&amp;lt;id&amp;gt; name Database to recover only_configuration Recover database configuration without data Returns Returns Completed successfully if the database was recovered.</description></item><item><title>rladmin restart</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/restart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/restart/</guid><description>Schedules a restart of the Redis Enterprise Software processes on primary and replica instances of a specific database.
rladmin restart db { db:&amp;lt;id&amp;gt; | &amp;lt;name&amp;gt; } [preserve_roles] [discard_data] [force_discard] Parameters Parameter Type/Value Description db db:&amp;lt;id&amp;gt;
name Restarts Redis Enterprise Software processes for the specified database discard_data Allows discarding data if there is no persistence or replication force_discard Forcibly discards data even if there is persistence or replication preserve_roles Performs an additional failover to maintain shard roles Returns Returns Done if the restart completed successfully.</description></item><item><title>rladmin status</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/status/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/status/</guid><description>Displays the current cluster status and topology information.
status Displays the current status of all nodes, databases, database endpoints, and shards on the cluster.
rladmin status [ extra &amp;lt;parameter&amp;gt; ] [ issues_only] Parameters Parameter Description extra &amp;lt;parameter&amp;gt; Extra options that show more information issues_only Filters out all items that have an OK status Extra parameter Description extra all Shows all extra information extra backups Shows periodic backup status extra frag Shows fragmented memory available after the restart extra nodestats Shows shards per node extra rack_id Shows rack_id if customer is not rack_aware extra redis_version Shows Redis version of all databases in the cluster extra state_machine Shows execution of state machine information extra watchdog Shows watchdog status Returns Returns tables of the status of all nodes, databases, and database endpoints on the cluster.</description></item><item><title>rladmin suffix</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/suffix/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/suffix/</guid><description>Manages the DNS suffixes in the cluster.
suffix add Adds a DNS suffix to the cluster.
rladmin suffix add name &amp;lt;name&amp;gt; [default] [internal] [mdns] [use_aaaa_ns] [slaves &amp;lt;ip&amp;gt;..] Parameters Parameter Type/Value Description name string DNS suffix to add to the cluster default Sets the given suffix as the default. If a default already exists, this overwrites it. internal Forces the given suffix to use private IPs mdns Activates multicast DNS support for the given suffix slaves list of IPv4 addresses The given suffix will notify the frontend DNS servers when a change in the frontend DNS has occurred use_aaaa_ns Activates IPv6 address support Returns Returns Added suffixes successfully if the suffix was added.</description></item><item><title>rladmin tune</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/tune/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/tune/</guid><description>Configures parameters for databases, proxies, nodes, and clusters.
tune cluster Configures cluster parameters.
rladmin tune cluster [ repl_diskless { enabled | disabled } ] [ redis_provision_node_threshold &amp;lt;size&amp;gt; ] [ redis_migrate_node_threshold &amp;lt;size&amp;gt; ] [ redis_provision_node_threshold_percent &amp;lt;percent&amp;gt; ] [ redis_migrate_node_threshold_percent &amp;lt;percent&amp;gt; ] [ max_simultaneous_backups &amp;lt;size&amp;gt; ] [ watchdog_profile { cloud | local-network } ] [ slave_ha { enabled | disabled } ] [ slave_ha_grace_period &amp;lt;seconds&amp;gt; ] [ slave_ha_cooldown_period &amp;lt;seconds&amp;gt; ] [ slave_ha_bdb_cooldown_period &amp;lt;seconds&amp;gt; ] [ max_saved_events_per_type &amp;lt;value&amp;gt; ] [ parallel_shards_upgrade &amp;lt;value&amp;gt; ] [ default_concurrent_restore_actions &amp;lt;value&amp;gt; ] [ show_internals { enabled | disabled } ] [ expose_hostnames_for_all_suffixes { enabled | disabled } ] [ redis_upgrade_policy { latest | major } ] [ default_redis_version &amp;lt;value&amp;gt; ] [ data_internode_encryption { enabled | disabled } ] [ db_conns_auditing { enabled | disabled } ] [ acl_pubsub_default { resetchannels | allchannels } ] Redis cluster watchdog supports two preconfigured profiles:</description></item><item><title>rladmin upgrade</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/upgrade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/upgrade/</guid><description>Upgrades the version of a module or Redis Enterprise Software for a database.
upgrade db Schedules a restart of the primary and replica processes of a database and then upgrades the database to the latest version of Redis Enterprise Software.
For more information, see Upgrade an existing Redis Software Deployment.
rladmin upgrade db { db:&amp;lt;id&amp;gt; | &amp;lt;name&amp;gt; } [ preserve_roles ] [ keep_redis_version ] [ discard_data ] [ force_discard ] [ parallel_shards_upgrade ] [ keep_crdt_protocol_version ] [ redis_version &amp;lt;version&amp;gt; ] [ force ] [ { latest_with_modules | and module module_name &amp;lt;module name&amp;gt; version &amp;lt;version&amp;gt; module_args &amp;lt;arguments string&amp;gt; } ] As of v6.</description></item><item><title>rladmin verify</title><link>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/verify/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/cli-utilities/rladmin/verify/</guid><description>Prints verification reports for the cluster.
verify balance Prints a balance report that displays all of the unbalanced endpoints or nodes in the cluster.
rladmin verify balance [ node &amp;lt;ID&amp;gt; ] The proxy policy determines which nodes or endpoints to report as unbalanced.
A node is unbalanced if:
all-nodes proxy policy and the node has no endpoint An endpoint is unbalanced in the following cases:
single proxy policy and one of the following is true: Shard placement is sparse and none of the master shards are on the node Shard placement is dense and some master shards are on a different node from the endpoint all-master-shards proxy policy and one of the following is true: None of the master shards are on the node Some master shards are on a different node from the endpoint Parameters Parameter Type/Value Description node integer Specify a node ID to return a balance table for that node only (optional) Returns Returns a table of unbalanced endpoints and nodes in the cluster.</description></item></channel></rss>