<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Develop with Redis clients on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/references/client_references/</link><description>Recent content in Develop with Redis clients on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/references/client_references/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Redis with Node.js (node_redis)</title><link>/rs/references/client_references/client_nodejs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/client_references/client_nodejs/</guid><description>To use Redis with Node.js, you need to install a Node.js Redis client. The following sections explain how to use node_redis, a community-recommended Redis client for Node.js.
Another community-recommended client for Node.js developers is ioredis. You can find additional Node.js clients for Redis in the Node.js section of the Redis Clients page.
Install node_redis See the node_redis README file for installation instructions.
To install node_redis, run:
npm install redis Connect to Redis There are several ways that you can connect to Redis, each with different security considerations.</description></item><item><title>Redis with Node.js (ioredis)</title><link>/rs/references/client_references/client_ioredis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/client_references/client_ioredis/</guid><description>In order to use Redis with Node.js, you need to install a Node.js Redis client. The following sections demonstrate the use of ioredis, a community-recommended Redis client for Node.js with build-in support for promises.
Another community-recommended client for Node.js developers is node_redis. Additional Node.js clients for Redis can be found under the Node.js section of the Redis Clients page.
Install ioredis See the ioredis README file for installation instructions.
To install ioredis, run:</description></item><item><title>Redis with .NET</title><link>/rs/references/client_references/client_csharp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/client_references/client_csharp/</guid><description>In order to use Redis with .NET, you need a .NET Redis client. This article shows how to use StackExchange.Redis, a general purpose Redis client. More .NET Redis clients can be found in the C# section of the Redis Clients page.
Install StackExchange.Redis There are several ways to install this package including:
With the .NET CLI: dotnet add package StackExchange.Redis With the package manager console: PM&amp;gt; Install-Package StackExchange.Redis With the NuGet GUI in Visual Studio Connect to Redis The following code creates a connection to Redis using StackExchange.</description></item><item><title>Redis with Python</title><link>/rs/references/client_references/client_python/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/client_references/client_python/</guid><description>To use Redis with Python, you need a Python Redis client. The following sections demonstrate the use of redis-py, a Redis Python Client. Additional Python clients for Redis can be found under the Python section of the Redis Clients page.
Install redis-py See redis-py&amp;rsquo;s README file for installation instructions.
Use pip to install redis-py:
pip install redis You can also download the latest redis-py release from the GitHub repository. To install it, extract the source and run the following commands:</description></item><item><title>Redis with Java</title><link>/rs/references/client_references/client_java/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/client_references/client_java/</guid><description>To use Redis with Java, you need a Java Redis client. The following sections demonstrate the use of two Java client libraries for Redis: Lettuce and Jedis. Additional Java clients for Redis can be found under the Java section of the Redis Clients page.
Lettuce Lettuce is a thread-safe Redis client that supports both synchronous and asynchronous connections.
Install Lettuce See Lettuce&amp;rsquo;s README file for installation instructions.
Add the following Maven dependency to your pom.</description></item><item><title>Redis with PHP (Predis)</title><link>/rs/references/client_references/client_php/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/client_references/client_php/</guid><description>To use Redis with PHP, you need a PHP Redis client.
Here, we show Predis, a flexible and feature-complete Redis client library for PHP version 5.3 and later.
Other Redis clients are available for PHP; see the PHP section of the Redis Clients page.
Install Predis See the How to install and use Predis section of the Predis client&amp;rsquo;s README file for installation instructions.
The recommended method to install Predis is to use Composer and install it from Packagist or the dedicated PEAR channel.</description></item><item><title>Redis with C</title><link>/rs/references/client_references/client_c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/client_references/client_c/</guid><description>To use Redis with C, you need a C Redis client library. Here, you can learn how to use hiredis to connect to a Redis database from an application written in C.
Additional C client libraries are available. To learn more, see the C section of the Redis Clients page.
Install hiredis Download the latest hiredis release from the GitHub repository.
Connect to Redis The following code creates a connection to Redis using the hiredis synchronous API:</description></item><item><title>Redis with Ruby</title><link>/rs/references/client_references/client_ruby/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/client_references/client_ruby/</guid><description>To use Redis with Ruby, you need a Ruby Redis client. The following sections demonstrate the use of redis-rb, a Ruby client library for Redis. Additional Ruby clients for Redis can be found under the Ruby section of the Redis Clients page.
Install redis-rb See redis-rb&amp;rsquo;s README file for installation instructions.
Method 1 Use gem to install redis-rb:
gem install redis Method 2 Add the following line to your Gemfile:</description></item><item><title>Redis with Drupal 7</title><link>/rs/references/client_references/client_drupal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/client_references/client_drupal/</guid><description>Install Redis for Drupal Follow these steps to install Redis as a cache for Drupal:
Install Predis under sites/all/libraries/predis. Download and install the Drupal Redis module. Configure Drupal To configure Drupal to use Redis as a cache, add the following lines to your settings.php file with the specified changes:
$conf[&amp;#39;redis_client_interface&amp;#39;] = &amp;#39;Predis&amp;#39;; $conf[&amp;#39;redis_client_host&amp;#39;] = &amp;#39;hostname&amp;#39;; $conf[&amp;#39;redis_client_port&amp;#39;] = port; $conf[&amp;#39;redis_client_password&amp;#39;] = &amp;#39;password&amp;#39;; $conf[&amp;#39;lock_inc&amp;#39;] = &amp;#39;sites/all/modules/contrib/redis/redis.lock.inc&amp;#39;; $conf[&amp;#39;cache_backends&amp;#39;][] = &amp;#39;sites/all/modules/contrib/redis/redis.autoload.inc&amp;#39;; $conf[&amp;#39;cache_default_class&amp;#39;] = &amp;#39;Redis_Cache&amp;#39;; In line 2, replace hostname with your database&amp;rsquo;s hostname or IP address.</description></item></channel></rss>