<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Redis Enterprise REST API objects on Redis Documentation Center</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/</link><description>Recent content in Redis Enterprise REST API objects on Redis Documentation Center</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/rs/references/rest-api/objects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Action object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/action/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/action/</guid><description>The cluster allows you to invoke general maintenance actions such as rebalancing or taking a node offline by moving all of its entities to other nodes.
Actions are implemented as tasks in the cluster. Every task has a unique task_id assigned by the cluster, a task name which describes the task, a status, and additional task-specific parameters.
The REST API provides a simplified interface that allows callers to invoke actions and query their status without a specific task_id.</description></item><item><title>Alert object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/alert/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/alert/</guid><description>You can view, configure, and enable various alerts for the cluster.
Alerts are bound to a cluster object (such as a BDB or node), and the cluster&amp;rsquo;s state determines whether the alerts turn on or off.
Name Type/Value Description Writable change_time string Timestamp when alert state last changed change_value object Contains data relevant to the evaluation time when the alert went on/off (thresholds, sampled values, etc.) enabled boolean If true, alert is enabled x severity &amp;lsquo;DEBUG&amp;rsquo;</description></item><item><title>BDB group object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb_group/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/bdb_group/</guid><description>An API object that represents a group of databases that share a memory pool.
Name Type/Value Description uid integer Cluster unique ID of the database group members array of strings A list of UIDs of member databases (read-only) memory_size integer The common memory pool size limit for all databases in the group, expressed in bytes</description></item><item><title>Check result object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/check_result/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/check_result/</guid><description>Cluster check result
Name Type/Value Description cluster_test_result boolean Indication if any of the tests failed nodes [{ "node_uid": integer, "result": boolean, "error": string }, ...] Nodes results</description></item><item><title>Cluster settings object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/cluster_settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/cluster_settings/</guid><description>Cluster resources management policy
Name Type/Value Description acl_pubsub_default resetchannels
allchannels Default pub/sub ACL rule for all databases in the cluster:
•resetchannels blocks access to all channels (restrictive)
•allchannels allows access to all channels (permissive) bigstore_migrate_node_threshold integer Minimum free memory (excluding reserved memory) allowed on a node before automatic migration of shards from it to free more memory bigstore_migrate_node_threshold_p integer Minimum free memory (excluding reserved memory) allowed on a node before automatic migration of shards from it to free more memory bigstore_provision_node_threshold integer Minimum free memory (excluding reserved memory) allowed on a node before new shards can no longer be added to it bigstore_provision_node_threshold_p integer Minimum free memory (excluding reserved memory) allowed on a node before new shards can no longer be added to it data_internode_encryption boolean Enable/deactivate encryption of the data plane internode communication db_conns_auditing boolean Audit connections for new databases by default if set to true.</description></item><item><title>CRDB task object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/crdb_task/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/crdb_task/</guid><description>An object that represents an Active-Active (CRDB) task.
Name Type/Value Description id string CRDB task ID (read only) crdb_guid string Globally unique Active-Active database ID (GUID) (read-only) errors [{ "cluster_name": string, "description": string, "error_code": string }, ...] Details for errors that occurred on a cluster status &amp;lsquo;queued&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;started&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;finished&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;failed&amp;rsquo; CRDB task status (read only)</description></item><item><title>Database connection auditing configuration object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/db-conns-auditing-config/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/db-conns-auditing-config/</guid><description>Database connection auditing configuration
Name Type/Value Description audit_address string TCP/IP address where one can listen for notifications. audit_port integer Port where one can listen for notifications. audit_protocol TCP
local Protocol used to process notifications. For production systems, TCP is the only valid value. audit_reconnect_interval integer Interval (in seconds) between attempts to reconnect to the listener. Default is 1 second. audit_reconnect_max_attempts integer Maximum number of attempts to reconnect. Default is 0 (infinite).</description></item><item><title>JWT authorize object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/jwt_authorize/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/jwt_authorize/</guid><description>An API object for user authentication or a JW token refresh request.
Name Type/Value Description password string The user’s password (required) ttl integer (range: 1-86400) (default: 300) Time to live - The amount of time in seconds the token will be valid username string The user’s username (required)</description></item><item><title>LDAP object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/ldap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/ldap/</guid><description>An API object that represents the cluster&amp;rsquo;s LDAP configuration.
Name Type/Value Description bind_dn string DN used when binding with the LDAP server to run queries bind_pass string Password used when binding with the LDAP server to run queries ca_cert string PEM-encoded CA certificate(s) used to validate TLS connections to the LDAP server cache_ttl integer (default: 300) Maximum TTL (in seconds) of cached entries control_plane boolean (default: false) Use LDAP for user authentication/authorization in the control plane data_plane boolean (default: false) Use LDAP for user authentication/authorization in the data plane dn_group_attr string The name of an attribute of the LDAP user entity that contains a list of the groups that user belongs to.</description></item><item><title>LDAP mapping object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/ldap_mapping/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/ldap_mapping/</guid><description>An API object that represents an LDAP mapping between an LDAP group and roles.
Name Type/Value Description uid integer LDAP mapping&amp;rsquo;s unique ID account_id integer SM account ID action_uid string Action UID. If it exists, progress can be tracked by the GET /actions/{uid} API (read-only) bdbs_email_alerts complex object UIDs of databases that associated email addresses will receive alerts for cluster_email_alerts boolean Activate cluster email alerts for an associated email dn string An LDAP group&amp;rsquo;s distinguished name email string Email address used for alerts (if set) email_alerts boolean (default: true) Activate email alerts for an associated email name string Role&amp;rsquo;s name role_uids array of integers List of role UIDs associated with the LDAP group</description></item><item><title>Module object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/module/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/module/</guid><description>Represents a Redis module.
Name Type/Value Description uid string Cluster unique ID of module architecture string Architecture used to compile the module author string Module creator capabilities array of strings List of capabilities supported by this module command_line_args string Command line arguments passed to the module config_command string Name of command to configure module arguments at runtime dependencies object dependencies Module dependencies description string Short description of the module display_name string Name of module for display purposes email string Author&amp;rsquo;s email address homepage string Module&amp;rsquo;s homepage is_bundled boolean Whether module came bundled with a version of Redis Enterprise license string Module is distributed under this license min_redis_pack_version string Minimum Redis pack version required by this module min_redis_version string Minimum Redis version required by this module module_file string Module filename module_name string Module&amp;rsquo;s name os string Operating system used to compile the module os_list array of strings List of supported operating systems semantic_version string Module&amp;rsquo;s semantic version sha256 string SHA256 of module binary version integer Module&amp;rsquo;s version</description></item><item><title>Node object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/node/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/node/</guid><description>An API object that represents a node in the cluster.
Name Type/Value Description uid integer Cluster unique ID of node (read-only) accept_servers boolean (default: true) If true, no shards will be created on the node addr string Internal IP address of node architecture string Hardware architecture (read-only) bigredis_storage_path string Flash storage path (read-only) bigstore_driver &amp;lsquo;ibm-capi-ga1&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;ibm-capi-ga2&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;ibm-capi-ga4&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;rocksdb&amp;rsquo; Bigstore driver name or none bigstore_size integer Storage size of bigstore storage (read-only) cores integer Total number of CPU cores (read-only) ephemeral_storage_path string Ephemeral storage path (read-only) ephemeral_storage_size number Ephemeral storage size (bytes) (read-only) external_addr complex object External IP addresses of node.</description></item><item><title>OCSP object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/ocsp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/ocsp/</guid><description>An API object that represents the cluster&amp;rsquo;s OCSP configuration.
Name Type/Value Description ocsp_functionality boolean (default: false) Enables or turns off OCSP for the cluster query_frequency integer (range: 60-86400) (default: 3600) The time interval in seconds between OCSP queries to check the certificate’s status recovery_frequency integer (range: 60-86400) (default: 60) The time interval in seconds between retries after the OCSP responder returns an invalid status for the certificate recovery_max_tries integer (range: 1-100) (default: 5) The number of retries before the validation query fails and invalidates the certificate responder_url string The OCSP server URL embedded in the proxy certificate (if available) (read-only) response_timeout integer (range: 1-60) (default: 1) The time interval in seconds to wait for a response before timing out</description></item><item><title>OCSP status object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/ocsp_status/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/ocsp_status/</guid><description>An API object that represents the cluster&amp;rsquo;s OCSP status.
Name Type/Value Description cert_status string Indicates the proxy certificate&amp;rsquo;s status: GOOD/REVOKED/UNKNOWN (read-only) responder_url string The OCSP responder URL this status came from (read-only) next_update string The expected date and time of the next certificate status update (read-only) produced_at string The date and time when the OCSP responder signed this response (read-only) revocation_time string The date and time when the certificate was revoked or placed on hold (read-only) this_update string The most recent time that the responder confirmed the current status (read-only)</description></item><item><title>Proxy object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/proxy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/proxy/</guid><description>An API object that represents a proxy in the cluster.
Name Type/Value Description uid integer Unique ID of the proxy (read-only) backlog integer TCP listen queue backlog client_keepcnt integer Client TCP keepalive count client_keepidle integer Client TCP keepalive idle client_keepintvl integer Client TCP keepalive interval conns integer Number of connections duration_usage_threshold integer, (range: 10-300) Max number of threads dynamic_threads_scaling boolean Automatically adjust the number of threads ignore_bdb_cconn_limit boolean Ignore client connection limits ignore_bdb_cconn_output_buff_limits boolean Ignore buffer limit max_listeners integer Max number of listeners max_servers integer Max number of Redis servers max_threads integer, (range: 1-256) Max number of threads max_worker_client_conns integer Max client connections per thread max_worker_server_conns integer Max server connections per thread max_worker_txns integer Max in-flight transactions per thread threads integer, (range: 1-256) Number of threads threads_usage_threshold integer, (range: 50-99) Max number of threads</description></item><item><title>Redis ACL object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/redis_acl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/redis_acl/</guid><description>An API object that represents a Redis access control list (ACL)
Name Type/Value Description uid integer Object&amp;rsquo;s unique ID account_id integer SM account ID acl string Redis ACL&amp;rsquo;s string action_uid string Action UID. If it exists, progress can be tracked by the GET /actions/{uid} API (read-only) name string Redis ACL&amp;rsquo;s name</description></item><item><title>Role object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/role/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/role/</guid><description>An API object that represents a role.
Name Type/Value Description uid integer Role&amp;rsquo;s unique ID account_id integer SM account ID action_uid string Action UID. If it exists, progress can be tracked by the GET /actions/{uid} API (read-only) management &amp;lsquo;admin&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;db_member&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;db_viewer&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;cluster_member&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;cluster_viewer&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;none&amp;rsquo; Management role name string Role&amp;rsquo;s name</description></item><item><title>State machine object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/state-machine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/state-machine/</guid><description>A state machine object tracks the status of database actions.
A state machine contains the following attributes:
Name Type/Value Description action_uid string A globally unique identifier of the action object_name string Name of the object being manipulated by the state machine status pending Requested state machine has not started active State machine is currently running completed Operation complete failed Operation or state machine failed name string Name of the running (or failed) state machine state string Current state within the state machine, when known error string A descriptive error string for failed state machine, when known</description></item><item><title>Suffix object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/suffix/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/suffix/</guid><description>An API object that represents a DNS suffix in the cluster.
Name Type/Value Description default boolean Suffix is the default suffix for the cluster (read-only) internal boolean Does the suffix point to internal IP addresses (read-only) mdns boolean Support for multicast DNS (read-only) name string Unique suffix name that represents its zone (read-only) slaves array of strings Frontend DNS servers to be updated by this suffix use_aaaa_ns boolean Suffix uses AAAA NS entries (read-only)</description></item><item><title>User object</title><link>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/user/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/rs/references/rest-api/objects/user/</guid><description>An API object that represents a Redis Enterprise user.
Name Type/Value Description uid integer User&amp;rsquo;s unique ID account_id integer SM account ID action_uid string Action UID. If it exists, progress can be tracked by the GET /actions/{uid} API request (read-only) auth_method &amp;rsquo;external&amp;rsquo;
&amp;lsquo;regular&amp;rsquo; User&amp;rsquo;s authentication method bdbs_email_alerts complex object UIDs of databases that user will receive alerts for cluster_email_alerts boolean Activate cluster email alerts for a user email string User&amp;rsquo;s email (pattern matching only ASCII characters) email_alerts boolean (default: true) Activate email alerts for a user name string User&amp;rsquo;s name (pattern does not allow non-ASCII and special characters &amp;amp;,&amp;lt;,&amp;gt;,&amp;quot;) password string User&amp;rsquo;s password.</description></item></channel></rss>